Oh my god, guys, I was sitting here talking to myself for like five minutes and like
Okay, well, it's good because you know what sometimes you'll say things and it's like this is like when sometimes
You have somebody you need to cut off in your life
You can write a letter
Know and you can write a letter you can say everything you ever wanted to say you can all the her open
Well, you do is then you just burn the letter
It doesn't matter if the reader or not. It's not gonna affect them anyway
They look at letters of the game. They look at all communications again
But you wanted to close it for yourself. So you write you write a letter second deep breath. Oh, I can get deep breath
Okay, so Vladimir you want to say stuff like this. It's just like a scroll and you know not welcome here
I'm I'm gonna have more strict rules my child because it's like I just can't have these these are monkeys running wild here
So Vladimir go back to your tree or the bridge well
So hi and get and mods. Please do not undo if I if I hide somebody a mod
Hey, you can't please not undo it. So let me see. Okay
And I didn't run away. It's like I was foreign bombs and
The other stuff say you don't get once you walk when you walk in my shoes
Then you can like tell me I'm running away. I'm doing this. I'm doing that
Spurging I'm crashing out. I'm this and that once you once you walk in my shoes
Once you live my life and then then once I live your life
I'll go and tell you everything that you're doing wrong and everything like wrong with you. Okay, but yeah
Since everyone else is so perfect. I'm just the I'm the imperfect one. I'm always wrong. I'm always
Something wrong. I
Don't fucking do this anybody. It's crazy. Maybe I did a past life or something. I deserve this as karma
Oh, yeah, my comments
Six minutes six days or six weeks. Okay. Well, I'll take my car and the karma can be good
If you do good things they can shape a good karma. It's not like I've fricking done anything bad
You might have been intoxicated a panel, but your attention's bigger. I don't know and I know those and I think you're my book
And it's like you're not banned and so they just as you know
Mod with caution or do very caution. I am what black black ends. What am I? What am I tell me what tell me what I am?
I'll take a deep breath
Tell me what you tell me what I am. Okay. Don't me to tell you what you are. Okay. I can tell you you are sue
Are you take my opinion seriously, and should I take your opinion seriously? I don't think so
so
Okay, your name is not going in the book. Okay, so I'm gonna see climbers. I'm going to book I
Need to get sorry
And all the white cop gaming, but I really know you so I need you I need you to ask me to do it
Sam is okay. Everyone's in there. Yeah, so, okay
I don't know if I'm gonna I don't know if I'm wearing black and either way no, I wrote double eyes double eyes
You see the secret guys is like, you know, no matter what no matter how much I spurs out or crash out or
Get emotional or argue or get upset or anything. I'm still also be fine. You know, I'll be fine if I
If I do have some some to the middle of the ocean, I will be fine. Okay, but I won't swim to the middle of the ocean
But like Catalina's right there so I can I'll probably retire. Okay, I'll be fine. I'll be fine because I'm I'll be good
this
This is for fun, but I'm also a capricorn capricorns are business people. I
Just can't I can't
I just I I cannot put this much energy devotion and I was just doing it for just for fun
I I could have I can't have a lot less any fun things a lot like so I could be
hooking up with the tons of people and
Going out of bars and all this kind of stuff. I prefer I prefer that I prefer me seeing out of trouble for the most part
Talking making friends that having
Well
You run away again
Run away from where where did I run away from just explain that here's be a very cryptic
Oh, the guy said it and I blocked him so now you're like, oh, it must be something effective. What does it mean?
You know, sometimes we all run away. Well, we all want to run away sometimes. Sometimes you can't run away. That's the problem
You know can't always run somewhere else and just leave everything behind sometimes we have roots and we we have things
We care about and so I I'm I'm I'm in here. I'm not bringing which from Earth or
Anywhere I'm right here
Right here. I've always been here. I'm freaking put my own address out my own address my own name
I docked myself long before you else could
So yeah, so again, we might lose some lose some people not lose them
But it's like in the chat, you know, there might be some good friends and we'd love seeing in the chat
It could be for months. I'm talking about this time of the day first. I'm talking about a lot of people. There's a lot of people
In a year from now, or at least people still be in my life or in the chat, most people
won't.
People, we go to different places, you'll get sick of me.
Different people, there'll be different chemistry, and so it's always sad, and I wish everyone
the best.
I'm not trying to, I'm really not concentrating on, oh.
Who else is live? I don't like to think about that because if I should have gone live, I'll go live
And it's like I don't care if there's five ten people in the chat
Well, sometimes it's like not that much fun, but I don't care though. I know it's like not as interesting as like
You know, well, I think my show is kind of interesting, but I know it's like not
But I don't know what you mean, but it's just like you're just like so bored. You're just boring user comments
You're not explaining so I just
Like you
You go hide. How I hide you. I go hide yourself. Hi. I never see you again
You are a coward sir. I'm gonna take you using either. So I don't like you over that guy's okay
So let me see if I can link up and no one's gonna come again. Everyone's right mad me. Of course
I'm gonna I'm gonna be the bet. I'm gonna be raw on the bed
guys
What welcome to the story, you know
Being me it's like it's just like a capricorn. I'm like scapegoat. I'm a person that
You must be oh it was there fuck it. Oh this fuck that part like it was gonna say fuck me and I say
I'm already expected. I already know I already know I was gonna turn on me. I
Saw I saw this whole it's not everything play before I came in that's why I took so long to go into it
Cuz I was like, okay, let's do the time it out right so it's just pretty much at the end of end of everything, but
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm pretty timing my capricorn, so it's Saturn Saturn is time
Kind of like the ruler of time
Okay, okay, okay, my life fish taco. I gotta have some fish taco
I'm doing I think about like five percent fish taco. I said the burrito is not growing out of my butt now and
Yeah, but the transformation is going to me so my black and I'll never see you again
You're not even in the book not worth my even a little bit of my ink. You're barely worth me my energy to click my phone
Okay
I'll do a page in this book. I'll be page
And guys, you know, go go page is why I beat his life. Oh go hang out with them. It's like if you like them more than me, okay?
It's
You know, what if I try to keep you with Emma like like she's got double D's
It's a playboy bunny. I'm like this like you dirty fingernail
You know skinny awkward weird person that you know, it doesn't deserve a second look. I'm apparently I'm very bad
So be this as you know, I never I guys if I
Someone's art. I would never like the music because I was like, I never saw the mr. Big Pies
I was saying it's not the right time to play your music
It's like sometimes it's not the right time to be giving a terror reading and like everyone's talking
I would not try to give a terry when there's nine people in the panel. I know that's a Michael. It's impossible
But beer is the glass one of them. But anyway
Why I never say to be there
Well, I did maybe jokingly. I said, okay, I'd do better hot days than you because she said I choose better tarot manager
They would do tarot. I actually do read how food, okay? And I respect it and then I said, oh
Every little thing I can be jumped on beta said my breath stinks. Well, how would she know I've never met beta?
How about you know, how about Charlie? How about Charlie? I'll never have to like
Bother with you ever again. You'll just be irrelevant to me. I hope your name's not read my book
I will be crossing out right now, but you definitely are crossed out in the chat for a good night. I
Know
That's why I'm trying to stay it's kind of like you care about someone and they're going too far
Say Alice was going too far. He was just like I
Mean he's like he gets this like
That's why I was saying demon. It's not a demon, but it's the kind of like a possession of a you need to break. Okay
It's okay. I'm trying to give room. I'm doing it. That's right
She's like, oh, you never take me never come I think well I go to your I go to your panel make sure you're you know
You're having a good time on your panel talk and some other go up somewhere
I don't I do my panel you come on talk online
I think I even gone without two or three days talking to each other. She's acting like I just abandoned her
I don't care. I'm trying
It's like you damned it guys. I was watching a reading tonight. It was a capital for reading
And they're like, oh, she's like, wow, you're Dan if you do you don't it's like there's no pleasing some of these people
They're not gonna they they they if you do if you're perfect
They want you to fail if you're if you're failing
They do something to fail, but you know, they won't maybe be interested in help
Yeah, so we're gonna be a break and as they and be like it's like it's like
everyone
Guys it our own channel our channel our own refuge and so it's like, you know, I want to be this channel
Everyone in her chat wasn't saying horrible things about me. She didn't say a word about it, but it's okay
Cuz you know, I know I sometimes I don't say words about it when you just said it's not anything like I'd expect
She was thinking up for me, but
It's still not a comfortable chat cuz everyone was like doing it and then and it's like I'm friends with Vita
So I I don't know why there's but yeah, she was kind of like going off of me for a few days
So maybe my
You're gaslighting a lot with her amusement like other trolls I've noticed. Yeah, I mean that's guys that is the truth
I mean, okay guys you haven't figured out the game yet. She is a troll. I mean she is
She is I mean it's like not in an insulting way or any kind of bad way and God is a troll too
It's like I got it. He's gonna come he's gonna come on and troll me
Gonna come on and like talking a fast voice with the tell the rules good
Hey, so he was
What is a good-looking guy in your picture? That's a really good-looking
I drew this for you. I drew this picture. I drew this in honor of you
You did it. Did you really draw that? I took an art class in high school. Are you are you the lord of the griddle?
You like it or not? I do. I mean, I see the cartoon that you really drew up. Yeah, there's more to it
There's like a cat and everything, but it's too big for the screen. That's so cool. I love that. Thank you. No problem, man
Yeah, and so the guy again, I just want to chat. Yes. I've
You know my best friend of over 15 years is a beautiful Russian woman. Okay. She's a beautiful Russian woman from Russia. Okay, is
so
anything about MK ultra anything about
Bio biochemistry psychology, I
mean
Almost anything. I mean I learned a lot through not from her like he was teaching me in a nice way
He was using these things on me
but you got to learn some way right and so and at least I was able to
Mostly reprogram myself, you know, it's like it's a process
You know, it's a first amount of stress disorder with a lot of stuff that goes with it a lot of cognitive dissonance
It's a lot of gas studies a lot of like
I'll do something wrong to you and then I'll get mad at you and it's a youthful of guilty
And then I'll just like laughing about it because it's just stupid you believe that you know
I actually got offended that you do something because I know about that stuff. Oh, yeah
I know all about
I didn't know you knew that stuff
That makes sense
If you did
Live stream earlier. That's why he's
What did I do now
This you're gonna believe this guy
Weren't you just talking about gas
You were talking about gas lighting
Yeah, we got two gaslighters. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is good
It's a psyche. Yeah, 25 dollars. No, you're gone. I did
You're gone. You're out of here. I got kicked off for 24 hours. That's $25, right?
You didn't donate them because of me. It's because of me. You got the money
Hold on. Hold on. So that means
That means wrong that means Ron donates to me Ron always kick clack
You know how many wrong how many times wrong every time wrong. I go live wrong gets clapped
No, I'm a Tom nigga. I made over four thousand dollars over. Okay. All right, man
And nobody and run there since he donated to me nigga. Give a fuck you got
I'm telling you what I donated $25. Yeah, you didn't donate. You didn't donate they're gonna somebody donated because of my actions
No, it wasn't your actions
I need to help JT build a channel you fucking
Letting these niggas over here fuck your whole
Arthur be the and diamond was cooking content without these losers these losers post kids and do wild shit
That's why I don't come around like that
Use what I do I stay in my lane and so I'm not I'm not going to another chance to see what are they posting exactly what's the story here
This is what they both do
You say I'm lying about JT got you say I'm lying
Okay, that is okay. Okay. I can easily clip this and tag
Sorry, I don't come stay with bitches and facts. Oh
Crazy night tonight, huh
Look
What does he want for me
Did you psych try to boost a channel up I don't stream anymore. What are you talking about?
Okay, no, no, but my channel is here to help anybody that needs help
My business let me cook papa my new business on your own man. Oh little man beat is not here to protect you
that you took all my guests and your uncle Ben or your uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle Ben or uncle
He's all he cooks about his kids. That's all that comes out of it.
That's the lowest form of human life is they doing that kind of stuff.
They just leave the kids alone.
They just think, you know, let's talk about ourselves.
I'm always speaking about it, all he ever speaks about.
Keep protecting that dude, Bita.
Keep it up, it's working great for you.
Yeah, it's wonderful.
Thumbs up, Bita.
Thumbs up.
Oh, sorry, Rita.
Yeah, you began it because you know we all...
Rita.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I was I was before start my show. I was watching 90 day fiance and so they had like a lot of
Commentary channels on it and those channels were having doxy wars where they were having private Facebook groups. They're giving everybody is
the kids preschools, pictures and everything.
It was just a fun TV show.
I mean, it's like, so people are just taking the shit
way too far.
Yes, Samman.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, why are you blaming me for what they
take away?
I didn't do it. I don't do that. We don't do that.
We don't do it. We don't do it.
I want to do that. I'm here to do it.
I'm here to do it. I'm here to do it.
I'm here to do it.
I
Special boy you read the bus
It's like, I didn't tell about boys.
You're out of the bar, right?
Love me.
I swear.
Don't look.
Yeah.
Yeah, because you're special.
They know about KK, but they don't watch me
We got to go got it. I'm writing your name
In the book
Going in the book
KK
Scott, come here in the book, Scott.
Scott, I know.
Jason told me everything about these two.
Arthur's a bitch too, KK.
Arthur's a bitch.
Dude, come on, dude.
KK, please come back.
That's what we need to be.
Arthur, Arthur, that's what we need to be.
Peter, Peter, come protect me.
Peter, Peter, come back.
Peter, Peter, please protect me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Well uncle Ben is very good right it is a good right and the people weed is one of my favorite
I'm getting so close. Can somebody make an AI of like the Creme of Weep box or the Uncle Ben's box with the Samman
pick. Yeah, make one right now. That'd be so good. Samman's home cooking or something.
I don't know. Samman's home cooking right there. There you go. That's it. There you go.
What's up motherfuckers?
Oh, what's wrong fellas? We love you. How are you doing summer? I'm doing great. How are you all doing? Good morning? Good morning?
Fantastic morning.
Try some trip cake. Better. At least give it a shot out to trip cake.
I feel like my twin's on the pit. Look at my twin. I have my little twin right there.
Your face looks so good, Psyche, with your shape. I love it.
You look so handsome. You look completely different.
I like ten viewers right now.
Thank you. Yeah, you can open in your fucking mouth. That's why we're going to listen
Well, and it's going to keep being fucking dirty bitch boy
You gotta fuck a pussy
Oh boy instead of fuck a man well because a woman comes up here you're fucking intimidating to a little bitch boy
It's not my fucking issue. Go tell your mama
So, you know in very a lot of music songs they say I love you baby, and then you can say
Dude his mom did give him enough fucking
Not my fucking problem. Here we go. Yeah, we've gone bitch. We've been
No, I'm just kidding. What's up summer good morning there. How you doing? I'm doing great. How are you?
Very good, man. It's a little chilly over here
I don't know how the fuck this weather works one day. It's chilly one day. It's hot one day
It's cold one day is raining one day. It's I don't get it
I don't get it. I guess that's why they call it mother nature, you know
You're a bitch connecting you're a bitch. Yeah, it's like it's like that
The same I like is like
You're the only reason karma's a bitch is because you keep following her that
We call her a cunt
You can call me whatever you want.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, you're nice. You're not a problem. No, you just want to the cons like how they know it in England
It's a firm and jeer men. So it you know
Bother me bitch your cunts never bothered like that kind of stuff's never bothered like, you know people some women are like
Oh my god, I'm gonna lose my fucking panties. I'm like
It's the man
Way harder than fucking a couple words. So a couple words aren't you you're not gonna survive as a fucking woman
Well
Have you ever noticed that the manner the manner so much like men like men these days seem like
I can't even say I can't even say this phrase, but I was born from Chicago
She say the bees are n words and n words are bees or something like that
Meaning like you know the men have turned into kind of like the women the women have turned into kind of the tough
Well, I won't say that. I say men are men. I mean, there's been out there that there's men, right?
And there's, but when it's a problem is you've got a lot of fuckboys that think they're alpha men
and it's like, no, baby, you're not. You can't even...
You can't even bust a nut in a fucking session. So you damn sure can't be a man, you know what I mean?
Like so, I mean, there's a lot of men that play that we're trying to play the or boys that
Try to play the mineral but you'll know a man because a man doesn't get bothered by a loudmouth woman
Okay, only into all we little boys get intimidated from that shit
I I like a loudmouth woman that it's like
But it's like as long as it's like not like, you know, just like yelling in my ear that I'm uh
Pussy or something like over and over well, but you don't give that you you're not gonna give that energy, right?
You're if you give that energy off then you're gonna you're acted like you're giving cinnamon energy off if you're a man
Acted like that. So then you get that with some kind of energy, right?
Well, but I do but I mean I do I mean I don't consider like pussy
Yeah, they say pussy or bitch even like I say that, you know, sometimes the people call the woman a bitch
It's like they take it as like oh like a strong like bad ass or something like that and I say and then if it's
Worst install, you know, so worse install, you know
So it's like and in pussies they worsen so for a man, but it's like for a woman
Actually a band of most men don't like being called a bitch over a pussy
All this deception is in bed, you know and in bed you wear anything you can say the n-word you can say
You can say you can say, you know, you can race play in the bedroom
We actually get off on these two
Okay, Arthur you haven't heard of race play have you heard of it?
I've heard of taking the breath before you speak helps. Okay. No, no, stop criticizing how I'm breathing
Okay, like let me talk right now. Have you heard of race play for the third time?
Yes, okay, so and then why am I explaining it? You already know why you're acting so shocked
I mean, it's like yes people like to be called those words and by
In a race almost it would be racist in any
And then it's not racist
Well, what you'll be called as race play what you be called, but I I was because you know
It's coming
Who what whose case was it that just came out here recently the one guy that has a YouTube page
That's super
And that white girl was calling him a slave and all that kind of other stuff.
They did a lot of race play in that that was a prime example in their court case.
If you look through it, it has all kinds of the race play shit, which to me is a
little weird.
I don't do that.
I feel like if you do shit like that, you have some underlined issues that I ain't
trying to fuck with anyway.
So, and I get into a lot of shit.
I like to be tied up.
I like, you know, I like, I like what some people would call weird freaky shit, but
that race play shit, that's just a no go for me.
There's like a really if there's a really dark black guy
He's like married to like a blonde blue-eyed woman, and they're both like super attracted to each other and
Then I guess a bat
Black man, and I'm telling you right now. We don't
Not even close
People will do blasphemy
I can't do that
Yes, I'm married to a black man 17 years. What's wrong with that?
Seventeen years have you ever committed to anything 17 years? Yeah, your mother
Yeah, well you would actually be a fucking man if my mom
But you were born by a bitch that should have swallowed you because she don't know how to raise a fucking man
That's the fucking problem. Why you see?
You buy you bother the black man can handle this and your little bitch ass can't is that your problem? Yes, that is true back at clearly
Thank you
You're the story of what happened
to me tonight.
Did you hear the story?
Did you hear the story of what
happened to me tonight?
You'll have a glass of wine at the bar
Okay, well, did you hear my story from the other night, I don't know if you heard it
So, okay, so I was like, you know a friend of mine like he I haven't seen him in a little while
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You ain't got to charge or whatever. I was like, okay, this will never I think
That's a you site
Sometimes
Bye
How you calling me that and you're
Drunk my meat
Why don't you to watch some fuckers girl?
Basically, I'm not really like into like just like that, but I kind of attracted this guy and
So I want to hang out here
Ray Wednesday, let me finish the story Ray. I use the backstage. Okay, so so we get back and then
Then he's like, oh, he's like, well, let me warm her up for a few minutes and I'll call you in or whatever
I was like, oh, yeah, I was like, yeah, right and I was not as the other guy
That's one of our it's been told be moved for people said this
And then we got with them closing the door or whatever, but anyway, so then
He goes in they go in and then like I was listening to music hang out on the couch and then I
Start hearing them having the doors open. I hear them having said
Go go go
And like real and not a virtual this happened in real life in two nights. Yeah, we're having two nights to go
Bye-bye. Bye-bye everybody. Okay. Good. Yes. Let's go. Sorry guys. I'm here for the second conversation. Yeah
and so so they're having so I heard them having said I heard about and I heard like
Well, I heard oh and I heard like slapping down our suction sound and I was okay
I was just like a lot going on and I was just like, you know, and then
There was, like, probably, I'm just guessing, you know, the explosion or whatever.
But then, I didn't see anything I heard, and then I heard, then he said,
Hey, John, do you want to hit this?
Okay, so then, then I, uh...
Was okay because they had the DMG pipe right a walk back there. Okay, so she's like laying on the bed
Kind of like like on her like, you know, they kind of like on her
They're in elbows. They say on her elbows with her just butt up in the air, right?
And then he's there with his legs like spray eagle with a full erection and everything and and then we were just
you know, I just
I'm not gonna like hop on anything until I'm told hey hop on so I was just like hey
What's up, and I just took the head of the pipe, and they're like, okay
You go charge it I showed so that was the story
I mean it's like it wasn't anything exciting, but I've known him for 15 years
He's never done anything like that and this for him to like have me
Come in the bedroom with you. They make it. It was kind of interesting. Okay, so rare you reply. Yeah, great
Please don't say the heart or the f a gg or just a no racial language
No, I'm not I'm not gonna do it again. I apologize for that by the way
Okay, no, that's what you're cool. You're cool. I'll write your name in the books
I'm writing summer's name in the book somewhere. Yeah
Thank you real quick. You do know this guy's here because the two other guys left
He's gonna do something so you gotta watch out
Who are you who are you I'm not going to nothing
JT is a huge Teen Wolf fan it's his favorite movie
Favorite movie. I just say a little bit on the back on that's why he's on that. He was okay, but it was like, you know
Not Michael J. Foster's that I mean
Your apartment for a hookup and left you out
I mean, well, yeah, he did come I guess they came on my bed
I mean, they mean they hooked me up and stuff like that
But yeah, they like yeah, he's like you should wash your sheets and stuff like that, but it was like
I mean, I was I was kind of like I wasn't into it would be insulting but I was into it
So it was it was fine. It was just interesting. It was interesting and I have watched my sheets
So who is that assholes who is that asshole in the top left hand corner?
Arthur
Arthur, okay, a crystal goes to see a hole god
That's his name. Yeah, Arthur like the art board. Yeah
You're who are you Ray one you sound very country
Where are you from who are you?
Summer you see what my fucking name says you can read can't you?
I'm from New York City
You a damn lot. I'm from the South, baby. You're not from New York
But you're not from New York
This this has the best degree is
For me we're but New York's or from New York City, and I go they go
And it sounds like this thing he said Ray is kind of like a crocodile done these summer viewer watch that movie
The Baconti the Baconti songs. Yeah, I don't know but I know he dams her in from the door
I didn't get that skill you have first
I'm right in the middle of Manhattan. I'm right in the middle of my hat man
Well, you're not from there. You're not from there. You might you're not from you may live there now
But you're not from there. I can promise you that that's not nowhere even close to New York accent
Goose is my occasional lover by the way
South or a different country
Yeah, it's either either call me Tony or you call me a lover. I mean there's no winning with you, man
You win both the way
Will you be my lover? I don't have a song girl. Damn. I wish I will you love it has a sign. I don't know okay
You took that shit. I complimented your headphones. So they were nice headphones
You said it was a princess Leia and you had a Star Trek fantasy you want to fulfill and I would help you to tell it
I died never once
I had to discord to best it. I got out of the distance. I have the whole message on the screen. I do have it
Well, I'm just kidding. Okay. Oh, so
Maybe job with a star worse than a Star Trek. He has a here. They don't listen to the Star Wars
They may have to go I hope he comes back. Yeah, what a chicken shit. What a total chicken shit
Uh, I ended my thing after that porn bomb and everyone's like, why are you is like, oh, thank you
Go run go out again. Well, I had to end the panther. I started it again. I ran right back, but
Okay, I can't do anything right
Can't do anything wrong. Can't do anything right anything in the middle. Yo, go shut the fuck
First
I mean, yeah, there's probably good points
I let them I let them I'm like, oh, please come forward. I can't leave them over
But they don't like come on a million different names and people I know and like wave and AI
If you're gonna say how am I if I'm always bitching make one what am I bitching about go ahead?
Okay, go ahead. I want you to let me push up and then you went on to shitting on Psyche's channel
You went on to say never one shit
I don't want shit on the channel, you know what I'll let you finish. Go ahead brother finish your point
You know it's such a fucking three chin looking ass up. I despise you, bro
Okay, well, that's a good claim. I mean the bird in the tree on you. Why do you do spicy?
Reason why I
Mean, I don't like you just don't like me in general. You don't like something. I said to me brother to me
I you've ever played Call of Duty
OK, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You can do with the weapons. It's just somebody on call of duty and they say it so it's like oh, it's you can say the worst thing
And then it's like open your books. Oh, so I'm like, I'm not getting them
No, no, that's what I'm saying. Don't you say it right? But that's that's that's the joke is that it's not funny joke
I would just have to have the panel and we start over it's not funny anymore
And it's not what I apologize that you despise me. I didn't mean to make you despise me. I mean
Who despises you you bring up a certain? Well, I guess that despises me
No, but you let me out. Yeah, I don't think so. You let me on your panel. So I don't think so, brother
I hear you need your own ghost. Your name is in my book. Oh, no, I've read it down. Go. So
No, my fucking name down. What's my name say in the book, psyche?
It's a summer and there's like a little heart next to it for a little heart
I'm just basically just writing everybody that I know in like on one section and I'm gonna put like
People that come on the show or they something happens on the show
I'll put like it's like some kind of record of that like if it's like oh this person came this way
I don't know. I got a nice look at the ZConn this reminded me of my show
Yeah, it's a little, and then I can write it and write it like if someone gives me an idea or they say,
oh, people always give me information and stuff, I can write it and I can shoot.
And so it's going to be like, and I'll maybe put it in my troll, troll-pedia that I'm going to write.
Everybody can contribute to that, by the way, and we'll all be famous, all of us.
What's next to your name? I said Doug's name is like a school of crossbones.
It's like a school of crossbones, Doug. How's that?
Or it's an answer picture of a wiener. So what's the question? Oh, wait, who has the picture of a wiener?
His name is Doug D. Oh, okay
I
Kiro psyche wrote some summer to flusie
Right one, please don't get me started on you
You're fucking in brain. Okay. So shut the fuck up. Oh rare. Oh, right. Oh my God.
I'm ready. Do you want me to let Summer decide what goes next to your name or do you want to be next to me?
Yeah, don't start with me because I like to get in my ass.
Summer can put no one's next to my name.
No, no, she better be quiet.
What are you going to do? What the fuck are you going to do?
What's the attention your mother never gave you? Is that what the fuck you want?
Is that why you think you could bother me this morning?
Don't play with me because I got all the fucking time in the world today.
I ain't got a goddamn thing to do today.
Play with me and you won't get a fucking word in, how about that?
Alright, I want to ask you, Ray, what was it like?
You better be careful.
Oh, shut the fuck up, you're a guy, you're gonna be a new and a guy.
Say whatever the fuck you want to say, say whatever you want to say.
But you better tell correct, bitch.
Ray, what was it like starting with Andy Griffith on the end of the video?
Well, say something, motherfucker, and stop talking.
Say something with some fucking substance, bitch.
Or shut the fuck up.
Okay
You want to talk shit? Let's go. I don't give a fuck
Are those otherwise I'm gonna fuck up your reading chat or not you go get what you get you want to play
I like to play motherfucker. Let's go
I
Don't know
Who knows verbal compact makes my pussy wet let's play
Holler
You were talking it dude go ahead
She didn't say
Let's fuck the play bitch
Hey, come on. Come on. You cowards got enough guts to play for what?
Ray you work
I didn't know she's gonna freak out
You have some more Ray you don't laugh you're left more Ray
No, we're ready. I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I think, I
Oh my god, it's like see I'm not finishing that now cuz you just made it weird man
See you always gonna make you always take it one step further dude. Okay. Okay. I'm sorry. Okay, but
Your nipples are hard
I don't I don't know who you are summer, but
You know, maybe one day you'll know how to act like a lady.
Oh, no, hold on.
No, wait a minute.
No, let me tell you something, little fucking bitch boy, okay?
Grab your, I want you to take your left hand.
I want you to put them down your pants.
Grab your nuts and make sure they're there
because you keep fucking playing with me
and you're gonna walk away with none.
Understand that.
Ray would you I'm grabbing them nuts to make sure you still have them understand what the fuck you're talking about
Sometimes you feel like a nut sometimes you don't reach down your pants right one and grab them nuts and make sure that your mom
You know you act like a man make sure you got some nuts there because before you come play with me
Fuck around and find out bitch
Well, he's he's fine. He's finding out right now from her. He's definitely finding out. I'm a bluesy
Well, why don't you scream why don't you us make it closer and see it's me good ass
It looks like a dumb dumb
I would like to take this time to apologize. I did not mean to call you dumb dumb.
I ain't worried about you, guys. That's good.
With lead and 10,000 people, by the way. Just throw that out there. Holler.
Hey, I'm not gonna lie to the kind of you know, right one just so you know, this is all for fun
I'm just talking shit for fun. So don't take it personal sweetie. I
Mean, we're laughing after everything right like it literally
Well, you know, it's the fucking internet have fun with it
Dum-dum trust me if you join more as you get you'll hear dum-dum quite a bit especially for me
No, I don't know about but no, I don't a drama
on my show or other shows.
I, yeah, you can catch right here.
Am I the drama on my show or other shows?
Like, I, I'm here to have fun and it's like,
and I don't, at the end of the day,
I don't think it's too serious.
I hope people look at offended by it.
I hope I don't offend people because I don't mean to.
I just mean to like, you know, have fun,
but some people will take it very seriously.
And though it's like, I offend some people so deeply
even if I kicks up.
Swap the panel for like, you know, who's the other day? Like I was like, I don't know
But he was on the panel for like a minute. They'll be like, oh my god
Like I did the worst thing I could do. Like you go. That was you go
I would actually like to go ahead right? Oh, yeah, right go ahead. No, you haven't offended us since you shaved your beard
I will say you look 20 times 50 times younger. You look you look amazing with your face like that. Thank you
I'm gonna say some shit. I'm not gonna say it because you're gonna take it a hundred. You're gonna take it a whole
The beard that's it's working for you brother
Yeah, it was my beer was wearing white
I mean literally like this year half of my beer was like what it was like Santa Claus what like what it was like
Oh, it's like a white hair
We're gonna have to get hold of that hair though the pigment is the pigment is yeah, you can call me thank you
Never offer me unless you were
Onto the hard R next to you your name is in the book. Oh, yeah, it was in the book
I have one thing to say though guys, and I don't want to bring this I don't want to argue
But it's like the only reason I got a little bit offended which I did
I'm not gonna lie to you
It's because there were certain people on the panel that like fuck with you and made you think a certain thing
And that's why I got offended when you blocked me, but I don't give a fuck. I always rejoin
I know but I just didn't know where it's coming from the Moz really. Oh, this was the I
Over five minutes
Gravy just got here
Enjoy summer
My son ordered me breakfast
Hey, that's awesome
Well, you know summer summer we call that shit on shingles in the south
I'm from the south baby. I'm from Kentucky
We love the south for you serious. It is the beginning of the south. Yes, it is, sir. Yeah, easy. That's like the middle of the whole country. Are you really? Yep. Really? Have you been to Kentucky? You would know it's the south. Kentucky, Kentucky is like the middle of the country. I'm telling you. And I'm telling you this is the beginning of the south. So come to Kentucky and you'll understand why I say that. So.
Okay, so if I I will have to drive north if I come to Kentucky
Well, that's why you're definitely probably more southern, right? I can see I can see that by your accent
Maybe Arkansas, Alabama somewhere along those lines and which I love those states because shout out to the South
But yeah, Kentucky is the beginning of this
Okay, uh, yeah, I know I was Kentucky's evidence out of the bluegrass and like the
Yes
Yeah, it's very
Let me know we'll have coffee. We'll have lunch
Yes, you are thank god
God does answer prayers sometimes
J. J. T. Is J. T. Is Kentucky the south it isn't it's
It's in the middle of the country
I think they can come up with a dead center. We are considered the South. Thank you very much. Thank you, JT
We literally got southern accents
No, because it's the South. Have you ever fucking been to Kentucky?
Lawrence my mom's from Kentucky. You know that I've told you that well, then you know that it's the beginning of the South
My dad's from Virginia. I don't feel like they're both right there
Like right there at the line. I mean depending that word for West Virginia
Some people kind of consider that like you know in it a little bit, but I would say
Summer is can't see pop there in Kentucky or is that like that she actually
That's like like to be all the way real. I mean, yeah people eat it and everything
But anybody knows anything about some good chicken. That's the last place you go and get your chicken at
that's how I'm going to chicken
chicken is a lot better than
That's chain style food, right? Like, you know what I mean? So if you go to like indies or different places other places
That's not necessarily like a chain of restaurants the food so much better
Hell you can go to some of the gas stations here and like they're crunchy chicken. Oh fire
Fire. Yeah, I know what I know what you're talking about on
I can't yeah, what you just said a crunchy chicken at the gas station. I know
Yeah, the biscuits be fired to the honey
Yeah, they be good. So you know like me my mom cooks better than any of that stuff
I agree my chicken is way better than any of that
But you know just speaking on like something you can grab
Like can't see it's just not what it's you know what I mean like everywhere else everybody's like oh, it's just fire
But like I mean there's sellouts anyway, they're moving to Texas
So it's not what it used to be no, it's definitely not what it used to be at all. It's so commercialized. It's just like that
It's like the last place. I'll get chicken up
So, yeah, well, I do know there's a 90 day fiance. There's a woman named Angela. She married this
She's like an older older ladies. She married this guy from Nigeria. She finally got it over the country and then she drove
Sorry, I thought you on oh, yeah
She's a fucking idiot she treated him like shit
From Hillers, Georgia, but I did see her get some gas station chickens. She's like this is the best chicken ever Michael and then
She was heavy she looked like dog the bounty hunter's wife and then she like all this like strange
Yeah, yeah, it's like she's like good
She got because then her like her skin on her neck got all like a chicken skin
And then she got she got like a pure a piercing on her lip and it looks like she had like a hole there
I mean it was and then uh
Brother, and then she was like she wanted to get pregnant like she's like Michael's family wanted him to have a baby
It's like 55 years old and so she was like well god damn
She went she went to the OBGYN and I knew like well, I guess you
I know it's possible, but is it probable to get pregnant at 55? No. No, but you can't you can't
But is it be sure is it probably not naturally not naturally, right?
No, yeah, you can there's women. They're good and even naturally you can get pregnant. Oh, yeah, but that's not
That's not the majority of 55 year-olds
Get pregnant naturally
Yeah, you can get
Yeah, there's women that have gotten pregnant in, you know, being older. I mean, it's not something I would recommend, you know what I mean? But like, yeah, you can't have anything that would happen after we're 95 till we did, we'd be squirting that shit.
So.
So I'm just saying it's fucking but hey, dude, that's an enemy dude. That's
70s making babies so yeah, let me get a pregnant. It is true
So be a be that yes, I did I did I did a reading this morning for someone be that and I also did a general for the chat
But I will do two more for members. I will
Summer's best friend
I got a question. Is it made of like your best friend somewhere? Yes. I mean, yeah, me me and Peter are cool. Most luckily
So second, do you notice like when your panel's hectic? Do you notice certain people on there when when that happens?
Well, yeah, I mean it doesn't start with a B
No, that's not let him let us be
No, I mean my piano
Sometimes there's nobody here and sometimes there's ten people here and it's like, you know, it's it's hard when there's ten people because
Sometimes at that point in the night people have been drinking and you know, I've been drinking and it's hard to keep up
And people talk yeah, I'm sorry
Okay, I get the amount of people but have you ever noticed like the actual people in the panel when it's
Alice is telling me. Oh, he's like, you know, um, so three diamond is you know page and beta is and the lecture
And but he's like screaming about it and then I say I don't think so
He's like, oh, yeah, and he's a yell at the man called your recharge is that and then on my own show
he calls you as like
as though I like Alex you can't like if you're not special he does that to every single person
he does it to every panel when he's it when Alex is in the mood to be Alex do Alex
he don't give a fuck about anybody you know what I mean that's just what he does but you know
Yeah, she is I don't know if she is beautiful and she is not well-matched, but yeah.
Why are you laughing, TY?
Have you ever, have you ever talked to her?
Have you ever, have you ever, have you ever talked to her?
She has her own unique voice.
Yeah, unique voice and it's, you know what that unique voice is called?
What? Oh, that's exactly what it's called. Okay. It's called a sport. All right. I'm gonna get into it. She ain't here
Well, she can join you
Rach, I like being a what's wrong with me?
Our voice she sounds really hot as the SM core what does that mean?
I got you brother. Yeah, okay. That's it. I got it. Yeah, but yeah
She never whispers
I mean
I want to hear assume be to just popping balloons and I want to fall asleep to that
That's that I want to hear the ASMR
Wanted to count down again that guy likes to ask some art beta. Why don't you count down again tonight?
Say can I did I love you? I love you. Okay, and then say you're not going to join
Again though
Scared her way. I scared her away
Yeah, we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we
Okay, okay. Yeah. Yeah, we were talking about that today. Actually, we're talking about the deliverance movie and like, you know
That's why you say you never talk to me
I mean, why do you have to go straight to that movie?
Well, I come on
I mean, I was trying to be like a little bit funny and stereotypical, but yeah, it is the kind of you know
It's not an iconic southern kind of
You know, it is fear that people have in the south that they go and they know buddy, but no they film that in Kentucky
They feel
Or about that they did
I'm talking to Joker tonight and Joker like lives in he doesn't Georgia, right? I think he was in Georgia
So he's like right, you know, he knows the whole he knew the whole story
What's that one place we have that one mental hospital here actually I used to actually live literally right down the street from it
Fuck, what was it called? And what is it called? It's on it. It's a big it's a big time mental hospital. That's
Can't take hold on
Is it what Ray is it called like a pig
No, that's not it
Deliverers
Oh my god, I'm getting a little bit. I was like a book. I've had the maybe Waverly Hills. That's what it's called. Waverly Hills
Thank you. You want to look at that like just do a Google and research it a little bit like that place is
It's like on the top
List of haunted place in the whole country like it's it's fucked up. They did a lot of fucked up shit in that place
I used to love the like MTV show where they had the celebrities going to like the
In band and mental hospitals and stuff. Let me see a way
Sense are familiar but
Yeah
Those shows those like haunted sleepover shows and all that shit
Goes there
When I when all that stuff happened with Brianna, it was literally like the apartments we lived in
It was right across. It was up a little bit the hill and across the street
I used to go to the park all the time
Sparked last thing with tea. Yes. Oh god, man
Yeah, it was right like the the hospital's right by those apartments
Because the park is really nice. They had a they have a really nice park there and my husband
I have to find the picture and sit put it on
On my community posts, but my husband took a picture and sent it to me
And I was like who's that little kid sit on Renny's lap, which is my at the time
She was real little my youngest daughter and it was it. I know people don't think I'm crazy
But that place has got spirits everywhere and
It's in the picture. So when I post if I can find the picture I'll post it
You'll be like what the fuck when I posted it on Facebook like all kinds of like
Supernatural people contacted me and all kinds of shit. It's like
Is it waverly
i'm telling you all that place is super duper there's a there's a
kickball that is known in the hospital like it's still to this day in the hospital
and people will go there and like the kickball gets thrown around everywhere people leave with
scratches on them like it's it's pretty fucking crazy i won't go in the hospital park like i ain't
I wouldn't call that badass. I'd call that kind of dumb. Honestly at this point because I
You heard if I go in there and I get like a scratches. Hey, I ain't going back up in that motherfucker
Stuff like that and I do definitely believe that there's you know entities besides us walking around. I want to risk it though
Yeah, I'm just I'm just
Readians and shit like I don't like I'll fuck around with it a little bit
But I don't fuck one of the two much because yeah, you better be careful
Well, I think if you use your region word, I've never once used one
Yeah, but it's a lot of it by nothing up in this one thing if you're really afraid of using it
And then you use it and then it's like it's gonna have like weird cards with it. You like no you use it
I don't use it. I ask you
Is always you raise these cards, but in the cards are just like if you look at the cards are evil
You might as well say like a children's picture book is evil because you know if it's any picture in any book
That's a good argument
You're using that story if you want to I'm not even trying to get into the day with you
But I that's why I don't I don't have I personally don't have a deck of cards
I think it's someone's intent right like behind whatever it is you're doing whether it's in the spiritual world or even in the
World, right? So if you're in sense pure then you're good
But if you have even just the inkly of ill-attent then you know you get what you get
Too much because you can't because when you're like
In order to set if you think you're sending some negative energy to someone else you first have to call it to yourself
And it's usually not gonna seem to like go so easily
Transfer from you to someone else is usually this is fit and fester and you if you call it out of the energy because the other person
Not gonna feel it. I mean imagine the work that way
All right a transfer there. Do you touch them like you just like tap their shoulder real quick and it's transferred
the
very dangerous. It can be. It can be. In the sense that if you're
sitting there doing a summoning ritual and saying, oh, any spirit
please come through and like give a message and that's kind of
that's that is an invitation. You open the door. Who's walking
through it? You don't know. You're the one. But also, but
there's there's ways to use things. Well, psyche, psyche,
you do realize that's how Linda Blair got
the
Yeah
That happened because of a Ouija board. Yeah, there are a lot of things
even in true story movies are
What's that word I'm looking for like just like enhanced like, you know, yeah, yeah in hands. Yeah fabricate it
It's like it tickled me. I don't know if you can see the tickle me
Dolls haunted and stuff like that
Once and want to fight then Hollywood it had been like a whole fucking we fought for five minutes
And then finally I won it's Hollywood. They said they don't say it's a true story. They say based on a true story
or inspired
Again, it's all about making the story like interesting relatable and full of like, you know
At all
Yeah, I think you know, right
Goats definitely has a point on that very like like yeah, it'll be like based on a true story or whatever
But even in true stories and stuff
We're still gonna enhance it to get that get that audience to grab their attention and keep them hooked. You know what I mean
That summer even inspired on a true story. It's the same thing same. Yeah
Most true stories say based on
True story they doesn't mean necessarily every single thing in it is going to be accurate
It's just based off of they've used somebody story and then they have elaborated some other thing
Yeah, they've actually got a trouble legally about that shit though because they say based on a true story
But like they go so far away from like how it's true. They're the real people was actually fucking suit them
If they use the people's names, that's why they change the names because the names are
changed to protect the innocent or, you know, we usually have a disclaimer saying this is
a fictional story.
I know that disclaimer, but when they don't do that and they say based on a true story,
it's like that's how they got in trouble, but now yeah, yeah, that's how they do that.
Remember this guy there's a guy he was on Oprah. He was like and he wrote a book
He was on math. I guess it's called a million little pieces
I think it's the book and it's about like there's all these crazy math stories basically
Basically each week you write this book
This guy gets his book published and Oprah puts out of the book club
Sells like a billion. I remember that
Yeah
He like he like made most of it up
It made all that shit up. He made literally everything up. I think he literally made it all up
And it was a best-seller got mad at him. Yeah
Oprah's
List over his list is gonna be bestseller, but yeah
She yelled at him
Yeah, it was crazy
I'm just looking at it. So, let's see my word for this book. So, how's everyone doing tonight? So, it's a four or five in the morning. Wow, the time is flying. Seven in the morning here.
It's six o'clock in the morning. I'm not gonna lie to you. I'm chilling now, but I did join to look for a little trouble. I was looking for, which I'm not even in the state now because it makes no sense in the state now, but I was looking for a certain someone to have a little debate, but it makes no sense to even say it now. We're all good.
for you
I'm not going to talk to you guys ever again so I'm going to come down to this right now.
Well, man, what am I what am I name starts to be here? So
You're right. I think I was very disrespectful and I really want to talk to her and whatever they identify as whatever it is
I want to talk to her because he doesn't woman very
That's really disrespectful what you just know I was being respectful. I tried to respect
We call fault false outrage he's also gaslighty words. Oh my god. I'm offended. You're gonna offend you
I think last night I got bullied by three or four people
Well, you fucking took that. Well, fuck it. Let's talk about it. You want to you want to run it?
Summer summer, I was trying to read for easy
I kept hearing uh, it was a woman's voice
When you call me summer remember when you call me tony remember?
Oh as old use goes okay this oldness, but anyway, so somebody still call me tony dumb dumb. It's not
News
Joking fashion
It was Tony dumb dumb, okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry apologize, but yeah
Oh
So I
I was trying to do the reading and I was like, I was like whoever's doing that. Can you just like let me just read the last sentence and I was having kind of
My eyes are a little blurry. I was trying to
I was kind of dark. I was trying to read the card
I was like just let me give you one second just read the last sentence and then as soon as I start reading again
It happens again
And I said it was another female. I said as they must whoever did that female moan female moan
You just you know yourself. How was it me? But there's no but there are no females on the panel at that time
Um goes there are no females. Oh, I saw him like a theme
I sound like it's yes. Well, yeah, you did say it was just I think
Growness why would I why would I disrespect your fucking pop?
I don't know but a lot of people do as well as a year now
Do I think as they as they mods? Can you just
Whoever didn't tell me who did it and they were wound and they're like
They said we thought it was good. It's like 10 number like five minutes. Yeah, they don't like me brother for the next three hours
he was
I let him back down. He was just like, it's hard for him for the next three hours. How'd you do that?
Why would you do that? Because it's disrespectful.
And he was like, for literally hours.
Was that not disrespectful?
It was like three in the morning. You're still talking about it.
I look back on it at 9.15.
That's seven in the morning now.
Okay. Well, yeah.
And we're still talking and having a good time.
Yeah, we are. Okay.
Yeah
And now he bought it up
He bought it up again tonight and last night Ray shut the fuck up. We don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Go ahead, okay, what am I doing? Are you talking to me?
You you started it last night and you bought it up again now
It's what you do cool. I'm upset. I remember that in a way. Is that okay psyche? Yeah, it's fine. What?
Yeah, you're resuming this. I need five. I need five bucks. That's fine
to reshape you ghosts
She's streaming this I'll take it out the next time you come to my panel. I'll charge you five bucks
I don't know. All right. We'll make it. We'll make it even next time we talk. All right
You don't know what you're talking about
We're on stream yard again
You're also
Okay, cool, we're not talking about that dumb dumb summer said she's resuming it that's fine if you're not
Be gone
Oh
Well, why are how old are you? I don't know
Why are you here, I'm talking to psyche brother
You know, that was but he loves the man talking like Ray talk
Yeah, right, what do you want to talk about talking? Yeah, why do I call people don't everybody a dumb dumb?
Yep, everybody in here. I there's only two people in here
It's kind of like I call them all the time. It's kind of like a friendly thing. You don't
Let me explain to you why it's not really that big of a
They literally understand why I call them that you're the one that doesn't understand that
Why are you getting so upset now that you understand it like we're all friendly besides you like why you I don't understand
What do you want? Right?
So girls when you say my dumb
You just want to hang out and be cool. That's fine. You mean you want to I'm gonna shut the fuck up
I'm new here, and I'm just notice
I'm new here, and I'm gonna be new what a jerk. You're new then you should shut the fuck up and kind of learn how it goes
Okay, right. I really want to like it. I really want to get
So so why don't you teach me? Why don't you teach me? Oh
When I say dumb dumb don't take offense when I say dumb dumb, it's almost like brother like that's my word
So what is it? What is it literally known for saying dumb dumb it's whatever the car whatever the car do some hazard is called
I want to like I want to get in the car with Ray and I want him to drive me around
I don't know like a field or something. I just want to I want to experience it south with Ray
This this like area of YouTube is that what you're saying?
Yeah, yeah, I'm kind of bent. This is probably what my um third or fourth time here, psyche
We do
This is his first time this is his he's new on the panel
Yeah, that's why I like when you came when I came in earlier
4th time on a panel. I don't
Hey, buddy, okay, it's not that I mean it's not that serious other serious
It's a why so serious like the Joker says right?
You know if you don't know what the fuck you're talking about you should probably be quiet in this lesson
Do you have something to say say it?
Well, yeah, but what are you talking and what are you talking about?
Yeah
Summer
I thought you'd be smart up to like actually be quiet and let us but yeah, brother come on in but you don't understand
I'm not gonna explain everything to you. We would explain like the past year to you
You should be smart enough to understand that like you're fairly new
Well, that's why earlier when you came in when you came in and you were like, you know
Reading the chat and you're you know reading some things they were saying about me
You ended up getting it because you don't say as what we do is we talk shit around here
And I'm really good at talking shit
Like I'm probably one of the best females talkerships. So yeah, she sounds like that's cool. That's that's cool
But don't ever
You would shit talkers, right? Well, don't pay don't ever take a new you're
Here what I have to say
I have hours again. How are sturdy would they would say they say they call it goofy on each other and that was a kind of like a
Mobile light term for trolling but the trolling on YouTube is not way beyond like the kind of goofing it goofing around
I said, I like to goofing around. It's like it's a harmless. It's a harmless funny fun
I call it a friendly crash out. Yeah, it's a friendly
Compact people get people get way too personal these days
So we have money for 20 I secure my burble judo
Here you are. I'm not bad at here. It's okay. If you
That has to make your somebody make yourself relevant just on YouTube so you fucking figure it out you fuck a piece of shit
So yeah, I could talk about 40s talking about drama I want and you're how old you are and you're nothing but a fucking piece of shit
So there you go
Sike post that link let 420 join
I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I
Also
Once you get to know people on the panels like you can like
What most people just know like is this they talking and it's like you can say anything
But if somebody like new comes in and starts talking to people and people people will get up and say like well
Do you know what I think about summer? Let me tell you the enemy. That's what I think
You love her. Yeah, you said I love her. I love you
You said I love summer summer would you like one more?
One more lap.
You're here.
Exclamation point.
Or make a point, ghost.
I'm making an argument for you.
Yeah, and all you are, Q, is a washed up fucking drunk.
So take that bottle and shove it down your throat like the dick it is.
What the fuck?
No, I'm smoking weed now.
I'm talking to the bitch in the chat.
Oh
Who's the bitch in a chat me I ask he knows who he is
Loser and like I mean you could definitely tell you're a fucking piece of trash, so I know you ain't talking shit
Fucking panel down because you're a bitch
It's dude
But some are really funny
Q45 is VB summer should we open up the panel so I he should be up a panel
We know my post is up in the lake, but yeah
QQ came on this morning. I like a few hours ago
Yeah, I let him on but he's like and I didn't do anything to his mic
He's Mike just a little working and then I was talking to him and then he was sorry
I thought I'm sorry to get mad at some and then he started
Okay
He's just a pussy me bullies people that he thinks he can bully and scares people he thinks he can
But really some of us know he ain't nothing but a worthless fucking piece of shit
And I think it's fucking fabulous
So
After what he did to you, I will never have any fucking help everybody's back for that piece of shit. So fuck him. Let me get a piece of
What do you do? Oh my gosh
No, they're queues this
Okay, that's the last time I was watching Q's channel
You know anything about wrestling you could never have
Because you would get cut down from the fucking route. Okay, all you can do is
In the fucking comments cue that's all you're gonna do because you're a bitch easy come up here at least you never had a fucking conversation
Back you I don't trust
He got a nosebleed when he was listening to
That's who Q is
Holler so I'll be trailer trash all day long and you're a fucking junkie in your mama's basement and gonna die from the bottom
You suck on it's a fucking great day, ain't it?
Holler. Yeah, but that that's my vision long man. She got another man
To the heartbreak kids song sorry Ray
Sorry, Ray. I just talked over you go ahead here. I think I'm sure I'm sure like I don't think there's a bitch ain't gonna join
I'll talk to you about
Is he cool or not, is he gonna porn bomb or not?
He
Kind of a sucker for a guy with a shirt. I don't know. There's nothing wrong with me. I just like, you know
That's what you're trying to do dumb dumb
I'd be like, I don't even know why you
Literally
Be your patient or VB. I don't VB. I think I know both of them
Oh, that's as pothock is a pothock is or no, I'm not very confused
Around my age a little older
Yeah, and she moved Q it Q is VB's boy toy. That's who he is right now
Well, you know, it's okay to be a boy toy. I mean there's something you know
Usually he's the fuck a bottom of the barrel of fucking YouTube. So like I said, what do you know what I seen him do to your channel?
Fuck him dude. He's a fucking lay low level fucking troll
Okay, they got in your head, but can't do nothing with your body to have substance no offense
No disrespect to you psyche, but that's exactly what he did
He took advantage of your time notes and got in your fucking head and
He's raking
I can give two fucks about subs, dude. I can give two fucks about subs
I have actually substance in my fucking shit
So you're you a shit and you're gonna die on these fucking YouTube streets sucking all the fucking bottle
You don't know what else you do for VP
Well, you remember I was I like what happened I was I was still as it's like three months into YouTube and I
Well, he did that's why he took advantage. He just tried to take advantage of you. That's all
I'll fuck it. I wasn't I wasn't even in contact with him. But yeah
So, um, what's your substance? Let's hear. I don't know. We gotta hear me
I hear you. You guys hear me? I just I just look the fuck into my micro next. I just punch my mic
He doesn't agree. It was great. This is actually late
So I'm I had a question for you one question
There's no funny that people try to take advantage of our boy would never when we're up here
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
a little bit of an attack in a second. I'm not, I'm not provoking people or trying, trying serious. It's like, you know, but
you do attack people that, sometimes that you like, but I'm okay with the brother. I understand. It's fine. I don't want to talk about it.
No, Psyche, Psyche's doing really good. He has a cool channel.
Hold on. Is it, yeah, okay. The version was a fake cute. Okay, so is that what I'm going to say? Okay.
Uh, Trump, uh, I don't, I don't, I don't want to talk about Trump. Okay. Let's see. Don't...
Make shit about it up. Okay. Thank you for being a nice girl here. So, yeah, summer's great
very nice very nice stuff actually look a wonderful one and
I think you all for thank you all guys for hanging out and no
Yeah, you join
Well dubs and don't make it about you. Okay, cuz it's not about you since you want to keep on
I love you to death, bro
But it's not about you wasn't talking about you so stop being shit about you or you can feel attacked all you what?
Then you're making shit about you and that's just weird so I'm talking to somebody in my chat
You feel attacked. Yeah, I'm reading the same shit. Yeah, I'm reading dub you feel attacked
If you feel attacked then fucking solve your problems. Not my problem. The fuck? Okay, somebody else
That's why I'm as fun
I'll take anybody at this point
You're not you're not worth the response of the guy maché and chat maché ex even though you're a member you're not worth the response, okay?
You know
So Q says who would you guess typing the litter?
Hugh one
Makes a lot of
Lettercube makes a lot of pop-up
Okay
Well, it was my conversations. I guess it was about that was me about me
You're inserting yourself if you'd like me to roast you dubs. I can you know I have no problem doing that
You're making something about you. I can make it about you if you would like I
It's it's definitely about me since it was my conversation that I was having about somebody else's a fucking drunk junkie ass motherfucker
Oh, oh, it's so hot just to shout. No one's gonna join you. He has to get up early the more this morning
She's just to join
She's just to show you just to say you're so ignorant
I just have to time you out for a little bit because you're so ignorant
You don't know you're talking about it just makes me cringe how I think being summered
I should make a good pair with me like debate together. I think we saw off each other to be honest
30 minutes to show the next time I'll be 24 hours. Thanks. Uh, uh, do you subsidize shit if you ain't making money?
Well, yeah, and I am making
That's where he's up. No. Well, and that's what he was saying like we he has more subs than us
But yeah, we're making money. He's just a drunk on the fucking internet. I'm gonna put it on something
Might as well put it on for him
Well, maybe I will hide you
I
Okay, you're back. I'd like to see how I mean summer due together
Oh my gosh, well, we disagree a lot. We might actually
Psych had a sad look on the space when I'm summer
Said she's been married for 15 years. I've been married for 17 years
I
Want to be the full boy better husband would never approve of having a male
He's gay, so if you're gonna have to hire a lady, I'm sorry, so I can't move to Kentucky. I'd love to sleep in like a band
I'm so depressed. I wanted you to be my full voice
I would love to I keep that pool so please here. It just so happens my new
You know
All right, we'll get psyche to come Wednesdays and Thursdays you come Friday and Saturdays and the
Can you stay in my in my in my bed in a in a lip or speedo and clean my pool once a week
You can lift it. That sounds about right
do you know the answer to that question do you know the answer to that question
do you know the answer to that question
you know do you know that is that what the answer is that's not what you mean
I mean it is it is it is a thing for like cleaning pool four times the four times a month and you sleep in my bed
What's the what's the problem so I keep stop fuck with me, bro
To psyches on Mondays and Sundays, how about that you gonna sleep in the bed and wear leather leather, too
I'm gonna be your pool boy. No, not
No, you have to be both of our pro boys. It's a package deal
17 years married 18 years together
Welcome every time I join our summer joins. I'll get her the credit you that everybody just doesn't join. They all leave
Well, there's 51 people in the chat. I think that you know, I think other than the joint 51. Oh, God damn
Wi-Fi get off of VB's Wi-Fi Q
I'm having a hard time understanding your excellent brother. I'm a little party psychies who brings the loop. Okay. Yeah
I just everyone bring like a gallon of
The pink cocaine baby oil for the slip-and-slide in that way. We should have not
Okay, I'll just clean my own
Go ahead and join because I guarantee I'll smash your logic guarantee out we can debate wherever you want smash
Free opportunity cycle let you up go ahead
Well, thank you. Yeah, I'll burn that ass up boy. Thank you. Thank you. I like you got me
But are you who is the guarantee? I'll fuck you up smash
Hey, that's big little bro smash the shit
Go ahead smash. Let's run that bitch dog. You could be a big big bro if you join and win
I like women's stories frame from that easy you should I don't know why you're not joining easy
I probably fall asleep before the diddy party, but yeah
What the fuck is that guy Q yeah join you'll find out we could be friendly. I'm not even saying we can bait join Q
We're just destroying
She wanted to be I'm down for who the fuck is that guy?
I don't hear you
People know
Sorry, I've never talked to you smash join the fucking panel. Let's talk. We don't have to debate. We don't have to argue we can hang out
Get around fast everybody knows who the degenerate locale fucking people of the internet is dumbass
and nobody knows you outside of the
you don't have to
I could promise you
you don't have to debate me
and so I watched what you did just like me
because you're a piece of shit
Q this is your
well actually I don't know this motherfucker
if he's cool
Q this join the talk
we're talk
If you want to debate, let's run that motherfucker.
You see if you want to debate, let's run that motherfucker.
If he was this like, if he was just like, like, you know,
if he was just- I don't want him with anybody.
Not being such an asshole to me, he would be really cool.
I mean, I like him, but I think he's a good looking guy.
I wouldn't even hit on him if he told me not to.
But- He's a fucking dipweed psyche.
He's trying to take your fucking panel down.
Stop. Stop being dignitized over fucking people
that don't give two shits about you.
Yeah.
But the keyword is try and you know me me and DJ electorate don't get along
But you know what she did a lot of shit for you to help you make sure that everything was good all the bulls that
He did fuck him. Yeah. Yeah, she does. She does. She does and prayer. What's up page page
Is that page is calm down a little bit?
She's an angel by the way, I would never debate page. That's the one person. I would never debate
Anybody else that wants to let's fucking run that bitch dog. There's there's summer beta and page on the on the screen guys
Custom are you gonna speed those three together? Yeah, and here's ghost. There's ghosts right there. Um, he's right to the left
So stop don't react like it's all Tony because it was you too
Whoa, I said
Some are you out here? Oh, it's not because he was a part of that shit, too
He's trying to put it all on Tony like he wasn't a part of that shit. He was a part of that shit, too
He's talking like God here goes Tony again. We all watch the bullshit
But you know, it's funny summer as I was there I kept I kept I keep saying like I might am I sure like hey
I'm like this is not like this is not West Side story
And I'm keep thinking like oh there's all these people that are saying there are gangs and it's like they're all like
You know through musical numbers and choreographed and dancing and I was like this is not West Side story
So that like looked up the plot of West Side story and it says
I'll just real quick. It says
Let's say it's right spot. Okay, so it says I don't know if you've heard what says story
It's about these you know gang members in like the 50s that were rivals and it's Romeo and Juliet
But it says yeah, it's like Romeo and Juliet
But the point was that the star of the fucking movies his name is his name is fucking Tony
He's like
Tony I forgot let me see if I can find exactly what his part was it says
It says in West Side Story, Tony is the male lead, a former member of the Jets gang who falls in love over Maria,
falls in love over Maria, the sister of the rival gang leader, Bernardo.
He's tossed out, he's based on the character of Romeo from Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet.
Tony's portrayed as an optimistic and idealistic young man, but struggles with reality.
He tries to leave his past, but the Jets, and the Jets behind, but it's ultimately drawn back into conflict.
His love for Marie is transformation of forces life. That's kind of interesting. Oh, hold on ghost is back here
There's good. Oh, do you think that goes with that nice story?
Wow, the fuck do you kick me?
I kick you you
I'm just kidding. I I accidentally push the I actually
Double tap back for the back button. I'm the fuck I very I very rarely will kick someone out, but sometimes
You can put him backstage though
Have it put backstage once because someone was attacking me
You would let me Adam, but that's okay
I mean
Like that we're trying to get people to join in them in a moment
The moment I get caught up in sometimes they make the knife fucked up next to the left my bad
Okay, it's okay. How's summer with you?
Who doesn't like summer brother I bother him. I hope I bother
Was much like, you know, you know, I can't you know it sometimes wouldn't like, you know, man
I can be you know zero content smash. Maybe you should join and make content
I think everybody a chat join
Curly here fucking reject that's who he say it not us
OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK. OK
That has summer sounds available. Okay. The mob
My channel is dumb dumb
You need to get a chance yes, you do have a song we got member we made you a song
It's got his very own song dumb dumb
Yeah, and I dedicate it to page
This is a theme of happy birthday and it's a happy birthday to you. I dedicated to page. She's my dumb dumb
Dumb numbs are actually delicious candy. They're actually delicious candies
Oh the house is so quiet now with spend all she just laughs and I'm just
You guys we moved my whole living room like around like a little like high school sleepover party
It looks so good in here. I'm so happy to have it refreshed
Yeah, sometimes it's nice to move things around and get new energy
My house over the last or my living room I got my living room everything organized everything off the table every
I just revamped it feels so good in here and I'm like fuck I'm gonna do that today too
Well, it doesn't feel like better. Is this you got banned because you said the n word on my panel you fucking piece of shit
That's why you got banned. So who said that?
I have a channel called hot mess summer and I have a channel called talk your ish Q came over on my channel one day
I let him up on panel. He chilled for a little while then he's fucking said the n word and he got banned because you're not going to
Say that word on my panel
Period so you said me. Oh tripping ugly. What the fuck? Oh, no, you're not banned. Oh, I'll say dumb dumb
You can say dumb dumb all day
So you said he said he said tiger, but he said the hard-ear of tiger
Inward with the hard R. That's what he said and he got banned
with the with the letter N in
there. You know what that
means. Yeah. Tiger without the
You know what? A card? A card? Animal card. Animal card. You didn't have a card.
Now the panel filled up that I kicked you and banned you, so I'm not lying, anybody can go back and watch it.
You were chilling for a long time with your fucking bottle that you sucked it on, your little alcohol,
and then you sit there for the end with the hard R, and that's when I kicked you, so...
Can I be a tiger?
And you're not black, so you can't say that word. Not on my panel.
So go I mean ghost. Oh ghost. You got the animal car for your face to tea with it. Thank you mojo
Thank you, sweetie. She's like we are good. You have to see
That shit
Because you have to see horse. Okay. You have to see horse. Okay. Damn it. You're the seahorse. The seahorse says straight
guys transformation feminine energy the seahors the symbol of power
frequently as frequently
On appeared on the coats of arms of European nobles and is associated with a ruler and
Valoran bravery
It was the seed of the Greek god Neptune or Poseidon the ruler of the sea Neptune was frequently depicted
large curly waves in a chariot pulled by giant seahorses. Seahorses' ability to
negotiate the ruling seas, a symbol of physical and spiritual
transformation, signifies
It's role as a guide in times of change because of its curving form and association with water
The seahorse also is in view of feminine energy
The feminine aspect is explained in the painting the emphasis of the painting
Swimming deeply women's deeply form on the creature's body
So there's a woman's form on the body. So it is kind of like doesn't page have a doesn't page have a
deck
Oh, are you on page?
Can you give me an animal reading?
No, that was yours for mine and it goes you can say thank you. You know the other you'll say fuck fuck me and like thank you
I appreciate it
You and appreciate it, okay
Okay, I like okay, is that you page first?
No longer gonna post
Protests in the street
Page okay, so page got the page you got the fish. You got a fish
The fish is it also feminine energy
fertility and abundance the fish is a sacred symbol to many people and all of us assume the form of
DT's and other supernatural beings as the creature of the water is associated with feminine
life-giving energy and often a character in creation myths the
The trio a tribe from the Cetropical regions of Brazil tells the story of
Parapoeta a fisherman who is visited by a spirit woman that
Rises from the body of a fish the spirit woman shows
Papa Roya had a cultivate plants and how to cook them go for it
And no more in the in the peck Indians of Honduras the nine-eyed
Mermaid Serena is the mother of all fish
that perched people would have special ceremonies before fishing to ask Serenia for permission
to take care of some of their offspring. In the painting the head of a woman is framed within the
body of a fish emphasizing the feminine aspects of the animal spirit. It's just kind of hard to
Yeah
My car I got to get mine now
Somewhere got the crow and there's the little crow and it says the crow
renewal transformation magic and abundance like the raven with which is
often synonymous the crow
Wheels powerful magic in Native American myths the crow restores order to the heavens a
Sue belief links the crow to abundance and prosperity what legend tells of a white crow
That warns the buffalo every time hunters approach
the this is the hundred
This needs a hunger and starvation and the crow is eventually captured by the hunters and thrown into the fire
But it escapes before being
Completely burned emphasized blackened by the flames black becomes the permanent
color as the crow flees and promises
Never to warn the blow of approaching hunters again the crow
Also the kind of phoenix that rises from the ashes symbolizing renewal transmutation transformation and the promise of abundance
There you go. And so you know psyche
I have a huge phoenix on the middle of my back. It takes up that most of my back. So that definitely fits perfectly
Just so you know, it's like yeah, I've been joined here for many times
I got many animal readings and the gorilla wolf or tiger is my main cards
Yeah, there's a good one. I do they repeat they repeat themselves not tonight though
I used to go on, I used to, on Emma's channel, you know, she would pull like an animal.
Yeah, I said, we're, we're, we're doing the re, yeah, but she put, but she would always
pull me like giraffe hippopotamus or it's like, it's no matter, she was like, like hybrid
animal.
Like, you know, and so if it, if it, the strange thing is she pulled like that combination
a couple of times.
So it was like, that's kind of, it's kind of weird.
APA.
Well, let's get in don't pull now. It's right. I can put it. I can put page on the side of the screen
Put her full screen, please
She has full screen
But we're here
You're muted, baby. You're muted page. You're muted
She's dogged
There you go. Yeah, you're good girl. Okay. You're good. No. Um, I'm just I'm really into this animal tarot deck that I have
I really I think I want to use this one
No animals that okay, let's run it. Yep. Let's run that. Let's run it
Go somewhere first
Okay, sounds good ladies first ladies first
Of course
Psyche
I love that. Oh, I like that.
Angry cat out of here. Yeah.
It's like the like it's like
that cat's name should be
or something. You know what I
mean? She's a boozy kitty. She's
a boozy. She's a boozy. She's
Summer. Shut up. Hey, hey, hey, where'd you get it?
Hey, hey, where'd you get it?
What is it?
Lockness, that's it.
Is it a goose?
Is it a goose or duck?
Duck, duck, goose.
We have the goose.
The love and care of children
could become an important part of your life
or people from your childhood
may return to it.
old memories can be healed or possibly old childhood dreams that are ready to be revived
you know what you guys i'll do i don't i don't just like doing one of any like i just well maybe
we'll do this okay no you got three people here i know that's okay we'll give her two we got some
i'm gonna give all of i'll give you all two parts i'm not gonna just do she's a goose
I just feel like it just needs to be a little bit more to the messages. I just feel like sometimes they're incomplete.
How can you be two animals? You're only one animal. You don't get one fucking card.
So because you're being is actually, you're being is all the animals. Like we're actually like we're all the animals.
We have every gift of every animal within us in some part.
I'm getting a little bit of bad energy. I'm not gonna lie. I know okay. That's why the Wi-Fi cut out Jesus Christ
Goes I think you need to get a stage and
Okay, good you want to stay up for the reading or you can't you can't behave yourself for five minutes
Okay
That's summer summer she said oh, sorry, sorry
I'm hogging summer string. Yeah shut up ghost. I didn't say stop. Sorry
Stop top bottom or middle
Top oh
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
Marriages are romantic partnerships in distress can still be saved so don't give up
So for me, this is just like all that love that you give that sometimes you
Don't much of it or to the wrong things without you're like being reciprocated, you know what I mean?
We've got all this in your last yeah
So this is a bit of a continued so you're going through those phases where it's like, okay, so I
I know what I value. I know who I give it to and I know what I stand behind and why I do what I do
But sometimes I still feel a little bit empty at the end of the day myself
So finding you know an outlet or a thing that fills your buckets because you know
We can have unrealistic expectations of others to be like us or what?
We expect them to be like because that's where disappointment comes in not everybody is the same, right?
right
For me, this is beautiful because it's like there's a lot of two so like two two two
purple
I would say a lot of green a lot of yellow and blue is definitely
The moon is in this one here. Um
With the water tower and so for me, that's just like that's harboring and holding. Um
Like you could represent a little bit of like a little bit like stagnant still water, but like still not like contaminated water
So it's like it's pure, but it's thick
So it's like, sometimes I feel like you have so much to give, but sometimes you're sitting there contemplating am I giving it to the right things?
Would I be maybe happier in this direction if I chose a different direction, but then I'd feel bad if I left this area of life that I was giving to.
Does that make sense?
Yep.
Like also being, you know, feeling abundant in certain areas, but also feeling like a little bit bored or like I might not be enough room for you to grow.
Okay, my turn.
Yeah
Anyway, that's pretty much the chance, you know look out for things in pairs
That's a good thing like you're gonna have lots of things come to you in in pairs and you're gonna notice
and also
You know if there's anything going on and I don't I don't like to call people that's not we're gonna be very vague on here
Cuz I know how it is here, but like if there's you know anything going on like if there's any like
What do you call it?
You know just agreements through like there's any kind of animosity between anyway, just know that it's gonna clear up
It doesn't won't sit forever. It's not gonna be right has to be drained and used to grow the crops
So it can be used as like experience to it's gonna send things different
100 show as always you're on point beautiful. Thank you. Thank you
Now your turn goes
And you know what I'm gonna put this back I'm a dedicated I'm gonna put it on four and then
Yeah, you're gonna work. I'm put on four and then we heard
You're putting on four of them. I don't know what that means.
Four and then, you heard.
Oh, four and then.
Four and then.
Yeah, four and then, you heard.
Is that four and then? What does that mean?
What's a four and then?
I don't know what that means.
I can pull up my own deck.
You know, it's like that four and then deck.
You want to do it now?
I don't know what you're talking about.
So four and then, like, XOR and IDF, four and then.
What does it mean?
Four and then, you heard.
What would you like me to use? Little words?
Okay, I don't want three cards. I want an animal card
No fucking I'll take three of them. Let's run that bitch
I
Look sluffy and slug
By the way, it goes with sort of the total skeptic. I think he's like big him
I think he's
Disrespectful brother. No, no, but I'm saying you
Let's see how this goes
May I ask a question
I was asking no, not you Paige. I was messing her
Do you believe in free will because I look hard that says like I'm like my
Let's just say that I have like all these crops and like the next day like I
They never got rained on then the next day you pull a car for me and all of a sudden the next day
I fucking move something all of a sudden all of something broke loose and they all got water
It's that free will is that magic? I don't understand or is that chair?
I think it's sorcery brother
so
Let her talk bro good argument
Okay, stop trying to bring me shit. It's really funny that you bring that up and it's funny because actually yeah free will
Four cards did come out for you. Actually. I tried to get
Okay, so we have the four of autumn and it's funny because this is the squirrel and
This would be this is like check for like pentacles or like earth and tarot
Okay, so like Virgo tourist Capricorn kind of energy earth energy. So be cautious. I'm a squirrel
Well, no, well, we you also have a few other things here, but like we'll just let you decide
Yeah
Be cautious about living life of extremes or seeing things in black and white terms
Consider for example, whether you are spending too much versus hoarding your wealth or giving too much emotionally
Versus building walls to keep people out
interesting
Okay, and Tony and Tony
Now fucking
Yeah, we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we're we
Okay
Your energetic and like outgoing and optimistic and you're very creative and your own endeavors and like the Monarch butterfly
It's like you do fucking stupid even follow your own magic
I'm gonna lay your ass out on this goddamn panel
Go ahead laid out
For you and you act like a fucking numb nuts fucking stop now he left because of you you're a fucking idiot
Cuz if she's gonna sit here and come up here and be nice and then he's gonna disrespect her and she leaves
Then he don't need to be on here either. Fuck him. I know it's ridiculous and it's like
I'm called for
Yeah, he asked and he was like kind of behaving like halfway through and then
He he lost that he did like I
Don't know. I don't know. It's just yeah, I'm sorry page page. I'm sorry and it's like, you know, I
Can't
Please yeah, he's a numb nuts. I love him to death, but he's a fucking numb nuts at times. I'll take a reading
They'll page is gone, but I'll read for you. I mean I do in the animal car. I can get you an animal car
Okay, well, this is animal cards are like oracle cards and so if you you might have like some kind of relation to this
animal or madness and a significance you can also
Research it, you know, I didn't see the symbolism for it and see if it makes any sense to you
But I'll pull an animal for you. Jaden is late. Okay. I'm sorry. I didn't pin the link yet. Hold on. So your link
So you are
Denizen, okay, and J when you might have to come over to psyche channel and to get the link
I don't know if it poses a man
Yeah, if someone's in both chats if you can copy I'll post them in my chat again
I just like I don't know how to do it off of my phone
But um, so then if you got the lion card and there's a lion, you know
Lion is very
You know, I don't know if there's some kind of fire the fire in your chart
But like lion is off, you know, it's a sign of Leo, of course. It's a triple fire sign
okay, yeah, so
It's a lot of Sun energy, you know, and it's like well in the Sun is a very positive card
Lions like also king of the jungle. So we have the king energy to it says courage
strength
Healing protection and life energy. We'll turn on the light once again
It says the lion has been a powerful symbol of strength and courage in cultures around
the globe because of its main and light color it has been associated with the sun, a symbol
of heroism and the source of life and energy and Buddhism for lion symbolized cursibility
and good luck.
it could cure any disease as well as protect a freighter from harm. In the
painting a lion is framed in a circle with four paints, four points, which
form a mandala, a mystic circular symbol that in Buddhist and Hindu
traditions was used as a meditation. The psychologist Carl Jung said that the
a holy place. It was means toward greater self-awareness.
It actually, you can see the circle kind of there. The circle is like a mandala, which is like a meditation.
It's really his first child. I know and but it's the and I think you know and he I thought he wanted a reading and he was
And he was into it and then he I don't know what happened. He's just
Hey, what he has yes, he says he crashed out, you know, he just crashed out a little bit
No, it happened tonight
I know and it's like I don't appreciate that and it's like and I will
Someone does that to me and I understand how we're just coming from someone does it to me like it happened on on the
People's podcast panel. I think I was trying to our good times. I was
Yeah, it was people's podcast. I watched it
Yeah, and I tried to like I was like during a reading and then they kept you know
They kept you know interrupting and like being disrespectful about it. And then it was just like it's just gives a bad feeling
And then it just kind of ruins the vibe for it. Okay
You ask for it even like he's he's definitely shared that he's not into it
Right, but then he asks us for it
And if you ask people to understand when you do stuff like that it does take energy and stuff like that
So, you know, she came up here. She was being nice and he'd like I taught him in the back
You want to fucking troll her? I trolled you all fair and gave him fucking war bitch. That's not okay to do
Don't fuck with her when she's doing that shit, dude
It's lame
Especially when you ask for
Yeah, exactly and that's and that's you know because it's like you know and his readers will usually not read unless you know someone asked and then
Then that's like you know, it's like an opening of the energy and then it's like if people have this like
He has seen that it's kind of like oh, he just wants to prove something about
Harris veteran. He always says oh what what we get the cards that says you know the sky's gonna fall
There's no car that says the sky's gonna fall. I mean it's like and if it doesn't rain or something and there's rain on the car
There's just a warning to
So, you know put on a
It could mean
He's mocking it because he doesn't really believe in it and he's mocking. It's cool to do whatever and troll
That stuff have a talk shit have fun
But when she's specifically doing that and she's doing it because you asked yeah, dude if you fucking troll her
I'm gonna try you back and I troll better
We're all having fun too. It was like we were it was like and then there's been like kind of like tense moments tonight
We're finally all like by being fun and then
You know, it's like it's like it's like a turd of the punch boy. It's like kind of the air. It's like he just has to like ruin it and
ruin the vibe and you know, it's like it's just up to show so so ghost and I'm gonna ghost your written in my book and now you're gonna get a little
Little frowny face next to him. Okay?
Kind of and then I'm gonna look next time you say something. I'm really oh look
Goes here. I mark the fuck out of it. You kicked me because I won or disagree
No, you got put in the back because she was doing something so and you're being asked so you want to market
and and and goes by the way like I don't know what debate kind of class or training you've had but you do not know
Shit about debate. I mean, it's like very big. I mean, it's like I I I really know shit about debate
I just know very little I was like a little debate class right but I know at least like
More than more than what you're whatever you say about debate is not how debates go you say I win
If they escort you at the building because you're being disruptive, that's not winning the bait
That's like that's like they win because you're out of the building. You understand it's like so it's not a win
you have to just study
Read some about logic and debate really really really research really study it because you really really want to do it
I know you really into it
But you're just you suck at it and to say I haven't even tried to win your debate
I won every time because all you do is like
That's a part of his thing though, and and you know what goes so he said summer should be smarter than this
I am smart. I'm very smart. I just fuck with Paige and I like Paige you feel me just like I like you
But you're fucking with her when she's doing a special gift dude, you know, I get it
It's not your thing and that's fine. It doesn't have to be your thing, right?
Like you don't have to believe it. That's cool with that. There's nothing wrong with that, but
Don't mock somebody that has it's a gift that she has and it's just lame as fuck dude when she's doing it and you ask for it. So
Bring your ass back up here and stop talking in chat. What the fuck? Okay. Well, he's under two names in the bag all the way back up one
Gross wait, what do you have to say for yourself?
What's up, uh
Go see but do you see like it was like, you know, you first of all you you did ask and so it's like at least if you
You asked somebody for she they came out of glass of water
She don't fuck with anybody if one thing if it was me doing it and you're trolling me or something
Or even psyche cuz psyche could be silly sometimes
But I still say don't do it to psyche cuz it's a gift but page don't fuck with nobody dude
She don't fuck with anybody so I'm not gonna sit up here and let anybody fuck with her
I mean, we heard by readings. I have a protected spirit, right?
Let us assume they're quick.
Yeah, it might be a retard, Lizzie, like, Oskar's at home.
If she doesn't listen, who gives a fuck?
Dude, it's okay. He doesn't bother anybody. It's one thing. No, no you were crashing out on her
It's one thing to fuck with all of us. Okay, don't fuck with nobody
Okay, then I understand that but you asked her to come up here and she did for you pacifically
So, you know what I mean if you're gonna fuck with her that I'm gonna fuck with you
I'll take a one
But you know I'll put you in the back with two two point seconds, you know that that's right
And I'll bring your ass back up and you know that
Dum-dum
Fuck would you go? I like you. You know I just don't want a page
I know you're not talking about you fucking shut up dumb dumb
Reading and you're on the panel goes I'll just kick you off the piano cuz you're not respectful to tear it is
You know that's
No, because you were the first time I read for you you were kind of like the same way, but I've read for you since then
And you're now
So I say you've been over it. Hey, so ghost
Pays to come back ghost. Okay. I'm gonna ghost if you if you fuck it up. Yeah, I'll just kick you off the show, okay?
Okay
Yeah
Those is harmless and I know that but it's still the fact like I said you're muted again, babe
You're muted up. There you are. Wait. There you go. Okay
Factual like I'm trying to message that you need to hear from like from
Not just from me. I'm not just sitting here barking at you wasted my fucking morning. I could be doing other shit
You know what I mean? I got lots of
I'm job so like but I'm just you know these messages are there for you and you can laugh them all that you want
But I know that like later in the day you'll think about it or it'll come to fruition or it'll resonate somewhere
And you'll be like down that's too big a little bomb
So we good again we do this every time are we gonna do this every time?
No, because everybody has you know, I have nobody here to defend me. So yeah, you're good
That's the thing about it I could say the same thing about religion Jesus Christ Mormon like
Well, now you can probably go fuck yourself a little bit.
OK.
Go.
Pay.
I don't like I don't like
What happens
Yeah, it's page her bubbles bouncing. Um, I don't know if I'm saying his name or her name right or wrong because I don't know
How to really whatever, but I think it's
dog Gaga
You can ask easy and you can ask a couple other people. I promise you're not blocked
I had Katrina look and you're not on the block list, but for some reason YouTube and psyche
I don't know if you have these issues, but like there's a lot of people that'll be like summer. I can't write
but they're not on my block.
Can you mute her because she's echoing?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yeah, you have two different blocked lists.
Yeah, you have YouTube and then one for your streaming art
and they're they're not on any of them.
I've even shown you have two Google blockless,
one for YouTube and one for your Google account.
And if you have a rogue mod block somebody,
it'll end up in your Google account.
Okay. Well, I wasn't that
Summer it took me a little while to figure this out and I don't know if you know exactly
But it's like a YouTube studio. We have to go to YouTube studio logs in through a browser on your like
Yeah, I know how to get to that one. I know how to get to that one.
It's the chat. Like, I have, like, DO, EZ, Dog Gaga.
A couple of people are like, somewhere I can't write in your chat and I just can't find them.
I've even showed them on live, like, look, no one's on my block list.
But, I've got a poor bomber.
Yeah, I should give that person a wrench.
I don't know if they mainly put their email address in your list of moderators that'll work, too
Yeah
Seeing that happen to like well, no, I mean cuz like talk your ass don't really unless you're a porn bomber
Which you have to come on panel, right? And I've showed easy easy easy even saying it in chat
I've even cuz people are like some of your line. I'm like, I'm not fucking lying like I'm not really computer savvy
You know like Katrina is actually who helps me with all that she runs all of that
So I'll ask her to look in the Google cuz I get frustrated. I can't find things like I just you know
That's why I don't even write in chat. I just push live and
And then I come on panel and say hey and talk my shit because I just don't do well with stuff like that, but
Go ahead
Yeah, can you fix your mic? I think your mic's a little bit. I'm not sure
Okay. Hey Miguel, how are you? Thank you digital? I'm gonna do that. I'm gonna try that
Yeah
Don't know why it's doing that because that I just know
For a second
But if you block someone if you block someone even if you're not a modded if you block if you block someone in a chat
They close out a different list. He goes on like a block like a block. Well, I'm only got like
Maybe three or four moderate mods mods and they've been my mods for a second five years
You know what I mean like if I do make somebody else a mod they don't have the power to block they can time people out
But they can't I don't give nobody that power. There's literally only a couple people that have that power
Yes, we're all good. All right, I'll charge that phone up and then I'm on the phone with you guys
I'll have you help me in a second. Okay
Um, I have a big meeting we're gonna so we're gonna we're meeting to just kind of discuss
So I don't know if you see but our event Saturday. What really good? Oh
10,000 people showed up. So now we're gonna do the delivery from that tonight and then plan for our next event
That's good. You'll be busy all day then
Later on, I think I was thinking about going, so they just opened, you know, we had all
those floods in Kentucky really bad, like everything got super flooded.
So one of our parks that I love going to, it has lots of trees and a river through it,
and it finally reopened.
So I might go for like a little walk and go to the gym, but then just chill for until
my meeting tonight.
Kind of do some grounding. I've been trying to get better at that.
Notice I haven't been losing my shit online as much as I was because I've really been working on that.
Good girl. Jonathan and John, John, are you here? Okay. Are you, are you not gonna form ball or are you a good person?
No
Oh, J1's one of my guys. He's good. He's not right. He has questions
No, I mean now now when I get up I can just roast and have a good time
You know what I mean? Like and have fun and not take it personal like yeah
So yeah, I said all that good shit, but it's not like
I
Was builds up it can build that pray and then yeah, yeah
Even I do it. I'll get a little
Most of it. I'll fucking lose my shit and then I'll have to leave for a minute and be like that's not who you are
Yeah
Yeah. Well, you know, that's, that's pretty much what it, you know, it's like, all right, let me take a little bit of time.
Luckily I've been busy. So which is kind of, but I miss everybody and I love roasted. I like having fun.
Like I like talking shit. You know what I mean? I love talking shit, but I don't like it when it gets serious.
You know what I mean? Then when it gets, and then there for a little while, my fuck is, it was just getting a little too real.
And I was like, yeah, I'm good. This isn't my cup of tea. I just want to talk shit. And then, you know, have fun.
And you see each other the next time you're like, Hey, bitch, what's up? And don't take it personal. You know what I mean?
But my fuck is getting a fee fee. So
Sometimes you just got to back up a little bit
We just we build up here, you know, and sometimes it's just we are we just too much
It's like a balloon
You know what I mean, and it just you much water balloon. Yeah
Let's go Miguel. What's up, baby? Hey, hey, what's that?
Yeah
Even like
I think a lot of readers would be very interested in co-hosting a page.
I think so many people in the community would just love a page.
So I think a page would agree with a variety of different readers coming on.
You know, if she can have a guest once a week or more to do terror.
I think, you know, but I think...
I want us to do a girl panel.
There's also a group of...
Wait, what are you talking about?
We could do ladies night. We could do yeah, I want to do a ladies night like you know
I think it would be fun just to have some
Because some women won't even come on panel because they can't you know, it's just too much
You know what I mean? But I think if we had a ladies night, maybe they would come up and hang out
And you know what's like would be really cool if you and I did a channel where we did tarot school or like, you know
Where we
Yeah, I would that would be cool. Yeah
let's get it sister yeah like i would be i don't know if you're talking about
will there be kitties we could all do it we'll be throw the kitties
stuff like that you guys and i hope then i approve
i agree i agree can i agree and that's it also goes in like the the direction of like i really
want like people on youtube like like the creators that collaborate with each other and do stuff
I have a way to like
Guys we should let them
Because people you know sometimes they what the crazy
Sometimes they want to tarot
Let's run that bitch dog
What do you mean say you're you
Look at it. Let's run it. Oh, yeah, you're gonna block
What's your name the what's the name of your channel?
Okay
I can't. I can't. I can't. I
can't. I can't. I can't. I
Yeah, I don't want that bitch. I don't want it. I don't want that bitch to show me.
I just don't I don't I like I don't I don't know it's like
And the peasants rejoiced
Horin a bitch fuck yeah, buddy. Let's get this day. I mean every like 10 seconds
He's like, oh, I want to do your channel like
And then he's like, oh, I don't want to go
What's that? I mean, I don't I don't it doesn't sound like I'm talking to like a
a rash a rational human being that I mean it's like I need to talk to somebody that I could say at least I can
rationalize
She's playing with the I had Dairy Queen for breakfast and she's trying to play with the bag
Summer, I got my little...
She's a little chunky monk. She's so cute.
I got her fixed and she got chunky and I love it.
I love her little pooch.
No, it's coming in by Lola.
That's Lola.
They do look alike in the face.
The whiteness on their mouth and their ass.
Look, hold on.
That's a little skinny.
Yeah, a little bit skinny.
Or mine's a little chunky monk.
They have the same color eyes, too, I think.
Can you put them by side?
Oh
I like what's up, guys? Okay. Hold on. Here's my other cat. I have to show you. He looks just like you're
My little Rbf like Lola has a
Hey, Lola, do you look at this you got like you can't like you can't leave a handsome fella with your baby
I don't know. I don't know where he is. I don't know. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is. I don't know where
Oh
No cameras, please I'm trying to sleep mom
She came over to steal my heating pad like to steal my heating pad
I got my little like my little like my light my like my walls and like tricks this sort of obsessing over the core now
It's like stop. I kept trying to pull away from the court
You can run and chew it
He just was going it's ready for and then I stopped him and then he wake I went to the bathroom for 30 seconds
I came out and the light was out. He'd already shoots her and though. I
Don't know. He just didn't like that one for that
Oh
Like primordial
She was so little before she got fixed. She was so skinny and I was so happy that she like gained some weight
My mom went to the hospital yesterday last night. He's got pain. Yeah, we see me
You see I went to four o'clock in the morning. Oh my god. I wake up four o'clock in the morning
Yeah, somebody called me
I'll be away to four o'clock in the morning then let on. Oh my god, they come I'm late
It's all your point of morning you links your mom
Yeah, I hope you mom. Yeah, I think they have that pouch because when they get fixed, um Gaga
Sorry Miguel my bad
It's okay
Yes, yeah, right?
Okay, I want a moment for tomorrow
So you can't you can't miss it moment for tomorrow
You're going to write tomorrow
Tomorrow more my poor way. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do my mermaids
I'll be there
All right
The Puerto Rican parade the Puerto Rican parade right Puerto Rican parade
Okay
I'm not sure I still, tomorrow I'm going to go to Korea and I gotta ask them
You know, oh the extra skin protects organs. Okay, that makes sense
Yeah, it's gonna be fun. I'm gonna be there. I'll be my bike
Yeah
Sharpey
I'm gonna bake my girl. I'm gonna bake you. I already baked you
You have an e-bike, right?
Psyche yeah, yeah, I have an e-bike. It goes really fast. I'm like it's almost like, you know
Yeah, my son has one he's like mom you couldn't use it anytime you want he has a flat tire
I thought about taking it out one day. The little sucker goes fast though. His goes really fast. Oh
Wow, the first night the first day I got it. So my sister was like, okay, well
There's just one rule for the bike is it's like you can't you can't drink and ride the bike
I didn't I was I had jumped in I before but it was like five in the morning
I was pretty sober up, but it was still a new bike and
The seat was too high
So I kind of like wiped out I was on the stream
I was like, let's go to Starbucks. I wiped out on the grass the library. I lost my phone for like an hour
I found the phone eventually
My my wheels are kind of alignment. My name was everything was fine
The dad I was kind of joking that I ran into a tree and everyone's something that ran into a tree
I did not run into a tree. I just wiped out on the grass next to a tree. I did not hit the tree. What are we?
What are we looking at Miguel?
Wow, that's Miguel's bike.
That's cool.
I like the green. It's the color of my cell phone case.
At least in Jordana's car.
The beautiful green.
I got my bike. I want my bike really fast.
I'm a little bit careful that people don't know about it.
So I want my bike.
And I want my bike for a long, long time.
I had this bike for 40 years.
For a long time.
I have it for Christmas.
You know
I love the color my mind is kind of just black like a white but you know, it's very
Utilitarian mind the good bike. I just got I haven't had a situation for several years
So I love it Miguel. You're the bike to Coney Island
Yes
I go with my black pants and my black shorts, and then I go over there, you know, so I go over there today, tonight, at 1 p.m., so, you know, I try to make it over there.
Yeah, I do. I do my swing, y'all. I do my swing until 11.30 p.m., 11.30 a.m. to over there, you know.
It's great to have Coney Island right there. Coney Island's a great place for content, I would think.
What's history and interesting things going on there?
Yeah, so that's all. It's a hot dog cousin. I'm going over there to the hot dog cousin. So let me see
um, there's a lot of people there. I'm Korean. So I'll be there.
Is it hot dog, hot dog eating contest? Or am I wrong? Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Okay. Got it.
Are you going to eat some hot dogs or are you going to let all the Japanese people win they always win every year
Yes
How many hot dogs can you eat do you think? I'm sure a little bit of a cook. I need two. I need two hot dogs, I want one hot dog.
Joe, just don't enter the contest. I don't think that's enough of the contest, but you know. Two?
He thought, if you enter the contest he needs to like stop, I think he needs to stop eating like a week beforehand and then like drink a lot of water and then like dunk the buns in water and...
It's a painful process of
Long time I went to the gym right over there the gym. I'll do an acid side for a little bit, you know
Yeah, this is a good bike doing acid sign. Oh, yeah, my leg
You know, let's do the acid side. So
You know, yeah, I went to the gym that time. I went to do acid that you know
I don't go as a sign all the way, you know
You know, so I'm looking on my Google account and yep, there's no nobody blocked except for people that I know for a factor like
Like not even for me
I don't know when you start getting these messages from those people, but if it's been in the last 24 hours
They probably were just tying up for 24 hours. Maybe it's not on the block
No, like easy and like Theo and and got like the doc the
God and a couple other people they've been saying this for a little while and I'm just like even cuz even like I'm on it right now
And it's just like there's the people there's only four people on there and it's none of those people
Community migration the good
Variation block list, okay. Yeah, so I don't know it is that that's where it was really strange
It's what I'm maybe there blocks because the only way I know to get around that is to give them wrenches
You can't give a wrench if they're not in the chat. It's the type that's the problem. Yeah, it's hard or you have to
Put their email in that, you know that same spot you were just talking about where you unblock people
I'm that I'm that same tab. There's the moderators tab and you can put their eat their Gmail in there manually
Yeah, I don't yeah, I don't I don't make just anybody mods. So I don't know if I do all that
Maybe I can I wonder if I can make them a standard mod because I've seen this happen over on now as far as the rinse thing
Go the TPP place. Why are you staying on it?
That happened to Wanda and they gave Wanda a wrench
And then I think it fixed itself after a little while because then she didn't have a wrench and she could be in the chat
So I wonder if that's a way to I mean not every single person that I'm gonna do that was especially on my hot mess page
I might talk your ish page like there's really no mods cuz
It's kind of meant like that
Yeah, I mean y'all you give everybody fucker lunches, but like it's crazy
You give everybody
It's very complicated with people coming on and trying to do things to the panel and trying to, you know, it's like, it's so, you know, it is like a little...
It's complicated for me, and so it's like I just know it's I'm almost thinking of just doing like you know
I think my link on discord is out of my shack. It's okay
Not but this is a perfect panel though. I love this panel right here
I thought you'd have a wrench. Yeah, I thought needs a wrench because I do post like links through the nightbot
And so you have to be a mod that has to be a mod that was the link, okay?
I thought I wanted to I want to get I want to get nightbot in my self
Yeah, it's really I mean that part is free. It's just like you know
You program yourself and then you know person help me like
Programming so it didn't like time on people for for the caps lock in for the
emojis, but so all it does for me is that if I type one of the commands, it will repeat the link
attached to the command. So pretty easy.
Doug's just back his dog can't get a wrench because Doug says bad things in my in my chat. And so he's not
You should probably go watch that video that I did since your eyes and your rod and Eli's met so big
Um, you probably should watch the video that I did on the whole situation which shows all of the situations
So before you comment a lot because you just look like a clown on the subject and nobody's going to jail
Oh, wow, I've got an advice for a fucking year. Ain't nobody wanted though. There ain't no one to nothing
Maybe they'll look best
And also before you take sides though the whole fucking story
Wow, I
Would need that that cat as more
I like that name a lot. This is Rave and Don Ebony.
No Ravey, do you just love everybody? You just love the North.
Kibbles and she loves me and pretty much all my cats love Kibbles and me.
That's about it.
Kibbles and Kaze. Kibbles and Kaze and Kaze and Kaze and Kaze.
Okay, so yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you have to give you have to give it I know but Brian Brian night night pot
It's not gonna mess with my answer. I mean night pot is just a robot that you know
I basically can program to-
Explanplug!
Yeah.
You put Explanplug or Budville and it will put a funny comment in my chat, otherwise it doesn't mess up my anything else.
It just says, you can give it also limited access.
You may get a standard model, but I mean, I'm managing this.
Yeah, I'm managing this.
I got an A bus or no?
Yeah.
Let's see my platform.
It's a cool, I think it's a cool
Yeah, they're actually like the things you can do if you can get really clear of its command on a Lisa's chat
You can type in like expression of weather or give you the weather or the country or the world
You have to give it access to your
Well, I don't think I don't think you do but
Doing a standard mod for it because if you only if you want to post links or else you can just have a safe stuff
But the post links that needs a mod, but I don't I don't think it does anything with the ads
I don't think it acts as the answer or anything. I just think it's part of the
general access
Can you drop the link again?
Bronzeberg, we're on psykins channel. You'll have to come over here. I don't have the link over there. My bad. Sorry y'all. Okay, I'll
Don't know how to do it
Sorry page. I mean, I hope you guys people are asking for the link
I was just you said the exact same thing. I was gonna say so great minds think alike. Oh, okay, cool
We're on the same page, baby
It feels good to just hang out for a little bit I missed everybody
Maybe not, you know, you should you should have a good morning
You should try to say I'm back
There you go
But not imagine a period of nowhere there are hundreds humans on that but it doesn't add sense
They why would they require access?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Here's my talk your ish one. I just picked up hot mess and talk your issues
What is that? What is that?
What was that was nightbot?
This is a nightbot. You see that's what you talk about. See. Oh, okay. Yeah, this nightbot
Yeah, I always thought it was like because money, but I was surprised to find it's like free and
Here's my talk your ish and no one's blocked on there
Yeah, yeah, we see a lot to use other block users that
No users currently blocked. Yeah
If they're not on that list and they're not on the on the YouTube studio list
Yeah, so there's
I don't know what it can be. I've never had a
Anybody YouTube does it sometimes. Yeah. Yeah, there's so much
Because if you give somebody a wrench it fixes it so it's obviously like a block for missions issue
You can leave Miguel alone because I'm not gonna play
Some of me means a page in the chat.
If you fuck with Miguel, I'll tear you the fuck up. No, no, no
Someone tell you Miguel or you in the chat. I just want to make sure I get I can make sure they're timed out or hidden
But um, this is the one saying about it. It says oh, yeah, I know I'll do big comment off Jacob
You take them go after yourself. Okay, you know leave my panel if you don't like to show you don't have to be here
And yeah, Miguel could come on panel. He has everything to contribute to the conversation. Yeah
Longs he ain't
And said dog Gaga you read okay, so the dog
Yeah, get a page. Yeah, you know the page is really like, you know, I got that. Is that how you say it dog?
I got I always feel like I busted it up
He's got like so much better
Not that she was bad, but it's like, you know what she was kind of shot and shocked a little bit
Some of the comments that she's first like I meant and there'll be you know comments in the chat
That's like really out of pocket and it's like and she's like really
I've just seen her, she doesn't deal with it so much.
Like, you know, it was like, she's not shocked anymore.
She's like, oh, she's like, go fuck yourself
in a really cute way.
Well, if y'all fuck with the people I love,
y'all can go fuck yourselves.
Yeah, I'm gonna like that.
So we have a really nice 58 people in the chat
at 5.40 in the morning, right?
It's Friday morning here for a Los Angeles.
Wonderful night
That's why I said as long as he's not a no dumb shit
Right now. He's straight. This is an Ari panel. He knows. I
We're gonna I'm a good and that's why sometimes they got also like, you know, they're sort of like taking
Stuff putting some people on the panel together just because it's like
That you know don't play well together
yeah
And then people like a blunder got mad at me and like
I'm taking them off the panel when it's like it's not like by being and stuff and just for a few minutes and then
The act of the guy I just take their dog or something like that. I just have something to experiment with it because the people are energies
There's different energies as a chemistry
And so sometimes they'll put people together you'll make a beautiful cake sometimes will like explode like a like dynamite
So, you know
Like a giant shit turn
right
Compatibility right some people flow together and some people don't your vibe attracts you tribe and sometimes you tracked other energies
That are kind of at your vibe, but you just quite can't and some people are fucking assholes
And they don't let it get along with anybody except other fucking assholes
But everyone has an agenda and everyone has intentions and so also, you know, kind of being able to like read people for a fact is like
Okay, I understand where that's coming from
But like if it gets at a hand like summer said like, you know, we all like to roast each other
We can all have to look good roasting or really fucking that's off. You know what I mean, but
We will all stand up real quick for each other, if it gets out of hand, and we won't play like that.
Like, you're not here to fucking push someone off a ledge, you're here to just kind of be like,
Tee hee, you almost fell, Tee hee, you almost fell.
Yeah, it's cool to talk shit and have a good time, and, you know, like, with Miguel's situation,
like, everybody on this panel's not gonna fuck with him, you know what I mean?
So, I know he's in good space, and, you know, whatever, but let somebody come up here and do something stupid.
Miguel leaves and we're gonna get in that ass
Like oh yeah, thank you protect people. I mean not for him to leave, but you know just like leave that alone. We got this
But we also know what to expect from each other too at this point as well.
We all hang out enough, you know what I mean?
Yep.
We're well acquainted so like you guys know what to expect from me, you know, if I'm gonna
lose my shit, you know, if I'm, you know, what I'm up to usually for the most part and
saying why I know what to expect from you guys as well.
It's just like when we like Alexander McQueen, okay, we all love hate, you know what I mean?
But he's our guy.
And that's the thing and a lot of is it's like we just know what to expect so then we're not really like offended or disappointed
You kind of just grow on each other, you know a little bit. Yeah
Yeah, people you're like summer. I can't believe you. You know, you you fuck with alex. I'm like, I do dude because I know I'm like
Yeah, he when alex is alex dude alex could be a fucking
Oh my god
He's made me rip all 10 of my fucking fingernails off before that's how pissy's had me before like crying mad
I was so mad at him
But at the same time, I've also gotten to know Alex, you know what I mean?
So there's, there's, there's a reason why that even though, but even though
he kind of went a little too far last time, so I'm just taking a little break from him.
That's his specialty though, Summer.
We know that too.
It was like, yeah, and that's why I take breaks.
Well, I've been dealing with him a lot longer than you have Paige.
So sometimes you got to take breaks.
Sometimes just because how he is is not an excuse.
That's what I was gonna say, there is accountability
and just because we all accept it
and like that's just who he is,
we kinda make excuses for the behavior
because then it's just accept-
I think he's beautiful.
Enabling.
Yeah, it's hard for me to deal with is like these personalities swings like
Crystal like crystal did I was like thank you. I love you. You know, you think I got your back
I'll fight someone for you. You're my guy and then she's like within like 30 seconds
She's like I'm sitting a gang to beat you up
I was like, what did I do?
I was like what did I do?
Boop that bitch was like you're this bitch Marcy and I'm sending the fence to your house, and I was like whoa
That's what Alice was doing tonight Alice was like screaming that that like
Um, the DJ lecture was was uh with piranha like and he was like
I think she's up piranha, I know them separately. I bit them different places. I think not at all
And he's like just so sure he's like screaming. He wouldn't stop
Hey, psyche. Can I say one thing? I think Alex would actually be a good fucking debater
If he was like if you just come the fuck down next you think about it logically like he'd actually be a good debater
Yeah, he's too emotional. He's too illogical. I get to say hurt some like he's actually a good fucking
Like not a good person, but a good debater if you think about it
Yeah, he's very calm. He's very calm sometimes like he'll be walking on his neighborhood getting into
We're gonna park and he's just like he's waving to these ladies. Hello. Hello, ma'am. He's sending ma'am and sir and so
And then and then at home, he's probably going bitching. Oh, oh, and so it's fucking
crazy. I don't know how it explains me like that. I would say a different word, but I'm not trying
to break TOS. He's fucking crazy. We're all crazier. We wouldn't be here together every day.
That's it. Yeah. And we kind of like, we kind of do get each other in a certain way. It's like,
you know, that's why it's like, I don't like anybody here.
Oh, come on. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got it. You've got
Not creepy you you always have to make it you always have to push it one step too far
Brother you want to come hang out with me? I'd be like yeah, but you got to be creepy about it, bro
Yeah, hey, you wouldn't come like you know
You got to be pretty about it, dude. I might have my peak in and we're taking a shower. I might peek in the back
Yeah, there we go. You're gonna be fucking right
Well, I won't bother you in the bed. I'll bother you in bed
I just don't peek now. There's I'll just join your pain and now I'm not trying to be okay. You can't you're not you're not welcome over
We're all if we all you ever get that Airbnb magical fucking masquerade palace that we all
It's like, there needs to be some
bouncers outside the bathrooms
keeping your ass out of them.
Yeah.
I mean, I'd rather stay with psych.
We have to walk out the fucking bathroom.
The pages there give me fucking terror readings.
Just give me a chamber pot.
I'll be there.
I'll be next to
go to bed with the chamber pot.
Thank you, brother.
We'll be doing terror reading the other side.
It'll be a fantasy vacation.
I
Came up to get a
Summer that's a summer you had to change it since to your herd because that
You're now on time out from getting any reason we do not have to ask you know until until you like come
Appropriately and that you know how to act. I don't think you'll work for you out. So probably never gonna read again
But if you ever do i mean i don't agree with that
Okay, we're here
We're the guest guys hold on one second because you know i don't fucking like that shit. I don't want to appreciate it
I don't
Friendly you see you should have asked if i don't i'm being friendly though i asked for a reading
Yeah
If i don't believe in god, but i come and join you
I want to explain, psyche is not being truthful, by the way, psyche this is why we have issues.
Oh my god.
What did I say?
Trouble.
Like to say things that aren't truthful and he uses other people's words.
And the same shit that that fucking that ziggie was saying is the same shit that psyche is saying
I get
And then I want to tell everybody to go fuck themselves
All right chris, okay chris. Let me say something chris though. So you
All right chris. So chris chris chris. I'll explain to you chris
So, what, what, what Ziggy said to you and you said to Ziggy were very different than
what I just said to the pair.
I said, I said, you kind of can flip on me a little bit emotionally.
You, Ziggy said bad things about, you know, taking, you know, taking, you know, the woods
and stuff.
I don't even know what you, the weird shit you guys are talking about.
I never said anything like that, I wouldn't.
I was just saying, you know, you sometimes will say you love me, then you say, you hate
me.
I was I was here that one day one moment. She loves you the next day. She called you an F word
Yeah
It's how she
Sometimes I think people are a little bit off on like their analysis of things and it's like it's like I can't like
rationalize with it, and so it is frustrating, but you love me or hate me, Crystal, it's okay. I still love you, okay?
I don't have any, no more feelings, but I would never say what-
I'm sorry to please everybody, that's your problem.
No, I'm not trying to please everybody.
I'm not trying to please everybody, but I'm saying, I like Crystal, and I'm saying, what she just said right now,
where I said, she's like, what I, what Ziggy said to her, I was, I just said the same thing.
No, Ziggy said some kind of threatening thing, she said some kind of threatening thing back to him. I was just-
kind of stating in a mild way
So why'd you get that was I wanted to explain but yeah
So, but I hope she does
No, I've never said anything like I'm gonna I never mean threats or anything and you know, I don't I don't consider what you said
He has right to me. I
I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around, I thought you were joking around
Okay, so first of all, you go stop mansplaining me first of all, you know
I
Know but even women don't need to be mansplained to it. We all we all understand like basic
I don't have any talk, that's all right.
I don't have any talk, but it goes,
have some empathy and know that I've been through like...
Empathy for what? Empathy for me?
For you bullying me and calling me Tony and all this shit?
Like, have some empathy for me.
For me?
For that red button.
Is that bullying you and calling you Tony?
Or asking if you're Tony or is that bullying?
No, I think...
Well, it says I mean it must be sent to install because I don't think he's that bad a person
I was just wondering if I don't know you had the kind of same cadence in your voice. I was confused. I apologize
What are you? Are you still going on about this? Okay? I haven't months ago
Didn't happen months ago like two months. You're the one still calling me it dumb dumb
I
The one that keeps calling me it
Okay, they're confused but he does
Under the name of ghost of amc right right text message to me with mini man
Dum-dum, that's Tony. It's Tony. Okay, but yeah, so anyway
Know I know it's not but they'll tell me dumb dumb and they're both name goes and so maybe I get confused a little bit
And accidentally calm joint. I really don't think it's doing it. Hey
Do you want me to add you you actually want to have the conversation? I'm down
You're too fucking stupid to have the conversation. You don't the fuck you're talking about don't have to run your own fucking
Fucking podcast you don't know what the fuck's going on
Okay, you don't know like you don't know what the fuck's going on
Why are you guys have no idea?
Who's that? Who's that?
But it's as close
No, it's you look at you. Are you are you being a man's brother?
Go look at the camera. You look at many man's brother. Are you many Manson? Are you being Manson?
No, I'm sexy
You look like many man's a little bit. Well, that's any man's in the truck. I don't like Tony. Don't um, all right
You just see me. Do I look like Tony Tony you dumb fuck?
You're talking about I just see I didn't see many man some with a short hair
So do I look like Tony done dumb fuck? Do I look like Tony?
Let's prove this once and for all do I look like Tony? I just my son like I'm do I look like him?
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Let's call me that it calls me in private. You're welcome. I look like don't call me. Don't call me. Is it okay?
I won't call you retarded if you don't call me Tony. Is that fair?
Okay, can I can I take that one?
Take this time to apologize. Have to know you to see your eyes
Okay, I guess
Oh
What is that there? We do not get me off
I'm not kicking you off. I mean you be right here. Don't keep an eye on you
I don't know. I don't know where you're doing or alone. Oh is this you can make it rain like if you
Pound it on the ground and dance
Hey, can you use that as a
You can make it rain. You can make it rain with the pole
I'm not gonna do that motion ever
Can you do that?
I want you to pull some of the pole
I would just take it and like I would get my speed and do it actually and then everyone's left
It's like a Polaroid picture
Yeah
All right, I'll make the American flag speedo would just be shaking so fast all the color of blood together
We like a purple it'd be like a purple color
House and had wine or a nice supper. I would give you a stemless wine glass
You're playing hand talker like me. I give you
A pool
I show page to the door
You know what I wouldn't even make I'd make your steak wrong and I'll come listen pull a car for me. Don't call me bitch
Good goes I just pull the car
Yeah, I
Pull the car free goes and says do not pass go do not click $200 go directly in jail
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
So I was at a teacher and she would call me Steve every time she saw me and I'd say that she'd say
Oh, I must have had another student named Steve. And I would never get to say, oh,
Okay, that's cool. Maybe your teacher is fucking retarded
Don't know but stop calling me Tony fucking retard. Maybe you retarded keep on me that shit. Maybe your teacher was retarded
down Tony
Your panties out of your butt your butt crack, okay, and it's like calm down, okay
That's why I know we're panties we don't get in wads that
B&J sandwich
Because if you didn't know what Tony was
No, it goes it goes if you didn't know who Tony was what you say you don't know
Then why are you so offended if I call you that name? Why are you so offend like so offended like why?
God you a bitch. Why are you so offended if I call you a bitch?
That's not in my name or anybody else's name, but you call me the wrong name. I wouldn't like
There's a person out there the same bitch a hundred percent
That's logical. So if it's actually possible, if I called you a bitch, why are you offended by it?
Antonio is not very good at logic.
Yeah
No, but it's a possible correct
This morning
I play the league of their own rules by panel
No, there's no crying on my piano. I did never once break
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You don't I don't fucking come by this be respectful
Do you know what do you know what?
You know the logical fallacy is you really would argue to me stop
With money without the is you're gonna keep me on mute me don't the fucking time
I'm dissing straight with a little bit of respect if you don't mind
Hello, I do you respect you're still here talking as I let you back. You're not you musing respect
You call me idiot retard dumb dumb
Stupid
You call page a whore and a different thing it's like
Page I
We called her you called her a name
Maybe hello, what are you talking about my name is I look what are you talking about?
Okay
I mean, I think you're are you arguing with yourself?
Yeah, I'm good
I was just saying I'm fine with you, but
these your debating skills are
No, it's like no other debate I've ever seen maybe it's like I'm appropriate debating in I'm not a debater
I'm not even a good debater. I don't even know how to debate. I'm not a debater
Exactly
But all you do though is all you do is debate you just admit you don't know how to do it or what it is
Hey, whatever
Oh, yeah, whatever whatever bro. Okay. What you just like trying to I'm so concede. What you smoking?
Yeah, I'm confused too
Summer when I chatted in the stream yard on Sykes that came up in
Updivit. I tied and I'm you bless your heart. I'm so confused
Yeah, I don't know
I've never had
By the way, don't talk to Tony like that anymore
Fuck are you from Canada? I
See you as you well. Hold on. Wait a minute. Let me go look at look at my last comments. Talk your ish
No, yeah. Oh, oh, I'm typing under talk your ish on yours, but Christine unders. Oh my god
I know it does mix the guy I understand her because it does mix together
Yeah, and then sometimes if you post through of the stream yard chat, it will post on both
But I'm not apparently so and since she's live on her came up through you it's showing
Yeah, cuz she's my close
I was like, what the fuck am I doing?
That's all right. I'm sorry.
My head's still spinning. OK.
So I just I saw them like, what the fuck am I doing?
Now you're strange.
I just want a little bit more.
I understand that.
They just come up on both.
After we talked, I got after we got off the phone,
I fucking crashed out.
I crashed too.
And it's not like that.
I got up. I had breakfast. And
now I'm sorry. We should. Ron, this is my first cup of coffee.
We had a few sips. Oh my god. Coffee time.
Coffee time. Sorry. I didn't mean to take that over. I was just
Miguel here. Was that Miguel? Yes, Miguel's here.
I
Even are you joining he said?
Motherfucker, you did it again. You can't help yourself
No, you're saying my fucking running you dumb fuck. It's even worse
Avatar say T why?
You're out of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game. It's half of your game
Don't be a good
Yeah, this is a
Miguel gets that I mean
Miguel gets
That's uh, this is easy way, you know
Goes you're kicked off Miguel's channel and goes
I
Okay, let's run that how did I get kicked off? Why did I get kicked off?
I don't run those channels then why did you fucking bring it up when what up?
You said I had kicked off a lot of channels.
I did not bring it up.
You need to understand.
You literally just said that.
Yes, I did kick off a lot of channels.
I did not bring it up.
Well, because you realize you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
You literally just said I had kicked off a lot of channels.
Well, somebody else brought it up.
Well, you're the one that brought it up on...
Oh, shut up, Rose.
Yeah, because you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
Fuck you, Rose.
I'm sorry, you got you got you got kicked off sides a little while ago. You've got kicked off summers numerous times
Shall we continue
Yes, Charlie. Good morning. That's not a good argument and you tell someone to shut up. That's not a good argument, Charlie.
I put Charlie if you want me to. I have no problem with it.
Would you like a document or not?
I want to know if you're just making blue cheese sandwiches.
The burden of proof's on you.
Oh my god, I'm not, I'm not creating you fucking idiot.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
Coming here, we're gonna be number one number two. I haven't banned anybody. So shut the fuck up
My claim is that you're an intolerable asshole
Can you tell I'm in a mood today by a claim as I don't know
Died QED
Cat or Sprunt? He does it better.
B.A.P. is the best slant chair I've ever seen.
I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't
Well, I mean that's a good argument. We don't want to hear either, but I mean it's not our panel
I can't fuck. I don't know so I would you like to hear me this morning. You haven't heard me at all this week
Have you?
Big apples oh my god those sound good holler the fuck says holler
I think it's like Arsenio Hall or something. I'm not sure.
I'm just saying.
Power.
and Charlie's making fun of us for being a hug box but look, we're all hugging and we're happy, yeah, we love, oh, Miguel, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
And hey, how do you have me tighter? Nobody's such shit to you. You have me tighter. Let's go home me
Yeah, see you Apple. Yeah. Hey, come on. You say, huh, brother
Now you said
It must have been some time.
I mean, I thought about it.
That did not get banned, Charlie.
You're next.
With that voice, you might get banned next to that voice.
You know, I really don't care.
Can you hear me now?
I've had a rough week to fuck you.
You sound like you had a rough life.
I know.
That voice is crazy.
You like to hear me now?
Yeah, yeah.
I know everybody on the panel.
I know, I know.
Okay
You're waiting for your balls to drop, okay
You're shot the 1943 ma'am
What are you cooking? What are you making?
Why don't you cook up some logic and an egg on
Toast the cheese bagels with jalapeno.
I love jalapeno bagels.
Yeah, that's not it.
Is money for 20 here?
Money for 20 just came in the shadow, am I wrong?
Money for 20.
I would hope so.
He's been in the fucking all night.
He's never joined.
The second one's for me, right?
What the fuck?
Yeah, what do you think of me?
A little dumb, dumb.
I won't catch up.
That's cool. I'm gonna crash out
Oh shit money I'm breathing in the mic, dude. Oh damn. There you go
Yeah, I say he's going like good 30 miles an hour
Almost oh god, there's New York people in here now
Yeah
New York people and you did a great live earlier. Yo ass is so high. That's why you got the munchies right now
You're muted. You're muted. You're muted. You're muted.
You're done done. You're done done. You're done done.
Hey, the shoe fits wear it, right? Okay. You got the munchies.
I know. No, but like it's also my daughter making her breakfast for school to take on the bus because they have swimming lessons.
Oh my god.
Yo, he's zoomin right psyche. You see this
Psycho you think you you go fast on your bike and he's smoking and he's recording. Oh my god
Please be careful
You know what he's doing you'll be all right
Trust me, I know I flew off one I flew off one it took a chunk of meat off my of my hand
I showed it on live. I had a hole in my hand. Oh, that's violating
Y'all remember who remember that I had a hole in my hand. I flew off the school
We have
Who are they?
I guess it was a wreck to come.
Hakuna matata.
Actually, I like Scar. I think he's remember who you are. I like to retard it. I like to retard it. Hi, you know
That's a dumb dumb high enough that's a dumb dumb
You know what he can't get right. He's a little different dumb dumb
No, you kind of rise me of summer
Yeah, I already think it was paranormal activity reported around
I
What I'll say wait, what did I say? I'm sorry
Sorry
if it does say, oh, kick goes, I will kick you out for the day, because you're being rude again.
Mike, would you do that?
Why would I? I don't want to kick him out.
What would the logic be behind that?
Why would you do that?
This idiot goes to the first one to say, oh, Paige?
Oh, I would never own this inspector.
And then, actually, a fucking card reading, this inspector.
What would the logic be behind if she says kick ghost?
Let's just say, hypothetically, she does say that shit.
What would be the logic behind that?
It would make it better if you don't fuck with me, by the way.
Yeah, go ahead. Someone's getting a little bit crowded and you know, there's kind of a high demand for these boat rides on the weekend. And so, you know, they can
Okay, you're gonna go on like a virtual boat ride. We're on a panel. Why the fuck would you kick me? Because she said that. I don't understand it. Please explain your logic behind it, which I know you're not going to be able to do.
Because she holds more weight than you do. Nigga, how about that?
Go ahead. How, how explain yourself. The burden of proof is on you. How does the how?
Okay, I wasn't even talking about me. I was talking about
Nobody's talking about me. No one said that word psyche listened. You didn't say listening to you is ear cancer
I was engaged with you on that.
Open your eyes.
Like I'll make your argument for you and then I'll debate myself. Should I just debate myself? Should I make I just debate myself then?
Yes, sir, I can do that but
She said to kick you off I'm gonna do that. What was the point of either saying that to me I don't understand that
Do everybody in the panel want to listen to this? Like you said everybody's tired listening to you
Okay, are those here? I made though. I made the argument. I made my own argument
We agree you win. You're the greatest debate that's ever lived see how good you are. Thank you
Kindly follow your own wisdom and yeah, fuck off to fuck off Island
Tony
The fun was like he had told you ghost is like always bringing and the peasants for choice
Always
He made his point and he had no other point except I I made a jack-o'-lantern
Now you're gonna finish my reading
You drew a lion card
Real quick psyche. Yeah, I don't know if you're aware. There's this channel. I happen to come across. It's called
Talk your ish. They're re-streaming you. I don't know if you know that
Yeah, I guess oh
I
Think for the update we don't think I don't know if you're aware of that psyche they're restraining you
He's here that's her channel. I didn't know
It was literally just psyche like I'm like what is going on did you find any other
Are you still on pale easy hello?
No, there's no resuming. I didn't see any blue blocks or I didn't see you
But so do you see anybody in the let me see I don't see me in the chat with that name
Okay
Just wanted to give you that heads up
What's up, what's up, what's up, everybody?
What's going on, panel?
Oh
That's my guy that's he's a friend of mine's
Oh, you know excited he said well I could go fast too
Okay
I'm scared of those scooters. The tires are mass small you hit a paho you're gonna go flying
No
Well, he's not gonna take my chat channel down lay mass
If they come up and say and he gives them permission, then he has to have permission to retream.
He has a button.
I'm re-streaming.
I'm re-streaming, psyche.
That's fine.
You know what that is?
That's support.
You sound like you jealous of his supporters.
That we re-streaming his channel.
I would make a post on my channel.
Oh, well, would you make a post?
Then go back to YouTube.
Share his content.
And that's how people on this panel that aren't from this community are on here because we're re-streaming
So we're bringing other people to this community. So pipe down youngin
They're not ringing much to the table to be honest. Well, you're not bringing what you what you bring exactly what you bring
Bring some neck you bringing that neck you bringing that neck like you say you was gonna bring
Sucking it from the back that's what you want to bring
I'm bringing the money to the table. That's what I do
I don't see any super chats
Donate in the back
You don't got to be exposed and you write a little message psyche. Don't say I don't say I donated
So like if we can be a donations from wherever
You say you see no donations no super chats. All right
So you made the claim that the new people here don't bring anything and then you were asked what you bring
They aren't the new people. They've been around you're the new people
Very well
You know
Damn after you put psyche to sleep look look artist so boring
You gotta say the inward like that. I mean like what do you think like to sit?
You're
You're you're like page why you turn off the camera. I was watching you cook
You can't fucking use any other word by life. No motherfucker. You're the ignorant one. All right cool. Salutes
See Jake Jake record what you're asking see that's official. I like how you do it right now
Thank you
Niggas put psyche to sleep. That's crazy. Well, Art Decade threw a put psyche to sleep
The tide of your shit fucked up the whole panel, bro
Such a doof it has
What you are you know, I was fucking ghost he left already. Now you guys got nothing to bitch about
What's that finally
Like you're telling me this guy
That's great for radio. Oh my god, that's awesome. Hey, nobody fucking talking dickhead
They didn't you know this didn't you notice what people was talking and fucking slow down
There's your over fucking shadowing everybody's voices with the fucking air in the background
Now we just don't have nothing to say relevant
I'm watching page and record cuz psyche sleeper anyways
Everybody get off so he could just go in the background and see if I can sleep them by himself. Yeah, man
So question is L though Ella Sam and you know us. Oh geez. Yo, what's the onions? I
Miss the OG's man. The old you're like
Someone sounds salty people say he missed the drama
Somebody's trying to make yourself relevant. I'm gonna get that neck. I'm gonna get that neck. Some of you mister. He was sick about
He got mad after he got mad after made him made him close the panel
He started violating the TSA rules and made him close the panel because he got tight
He got tight that Arthur was Arthur was saying he would give psyche some neck
I was laughing neck neck
3000 and he says something crazy and that's like he closed it
You got mad.
What do we talk about dude, what do we talk why you embarrassed why you embarrassed the guy easy stop it come on
This is exactly what he say oh if we was in the shower and and and I'll do something and we was naked or something
He's they all give you the neck the neck. What?
And then he got mad and he said something that made psyche take down a paneling and he did it on purpose because he got exposed
He probably thought it wasn't live, he probably thought it was just, you know,
on the street, like, he's not gonna remember that?
Or, like, he's thinking down, is that true? Get out of here!
You sure? I said I would give him neck or did I say I would give him neck?
You said you would give him neck, neck, 3,000.
Yeah, expose, expose.
It's Conte, right? It's okay. It's okay. It's Conte, right?
You missed the drama. You missed the drama.
Hit the drama. I'm bringing the drama to you.
You missed it, right? But now you don't like it because it's toward you, right?
It's towards Arthur, so Arthur don't like the drama.
When you giving that guap guap 3,000, huh?
Another thing is manipulating the truth. That's what you're doing right now.
Well, I heard what I heard and then you got bad and you said a couple things to take that
Loves it. He loves it. What's that? What's this month problem? I bought on problem. He can have it
Yeah, I think that's pretty cool you but now that I know you manipulate the truth now
I know in the future
whatever comes out of your mouth I can't take it for you know 100% because I know now you manipulate
the truth. You love the job, but what the job is on you? Where are you at? Are you crying?
That's not like you bitch. You voted. There's a difference between truth and manipulate and the truth.
You said Gua Gua 3000. I know a bunch of the chat is going to be here like
You said you said you said you was gonna give him the head
The neck okay, so you say you say yo we're using the shower together what you're gonna do
I'm gonna give you that neck
Hold on. Did you say that matter of fact J dog was in here with me? Where J dog at J dog perform guy
J-Dog was there with me with me J-Dog you and him and he asked you about a sour question
You got mad cuz you said neck you slipped up and say you don't give him the neck and then J-Dog was like hold on
Did I hear you say you gonna give him neck and I was like, yeah
3000 exactly how it went down. Let's go
All right, cool, I know now in the future. I can't trust you. You're only doing yourself some harm. That's all
I'm gonna hold it down like Nino Brown and be quiet. You're
Oh, he got mad. He got re-raised quit. Did he raise quit people?
I made him raise quit.
That's nice
That ain't nice
I ain't mean to I ain't mean to people. I made Arthur raise quit go out. Go out 3000 rage quit it
Hopefully he's okay
Somebody check on him
Give him a give him a phone call people. Wellness wellness check
Friendship check friendship check if anybody's this right
Shit, see chat is what happens when you get caught up in the mix
You know you say he missed the old people that bring all the drama, so you know I'm saying so I'll bring the drama
There you go. We couldn't handle it
Probably because they didn't expose them before, you know what I mean? Now you expose them
So to make it tight
No
J-dog could confirm it J-dog had the fresh cut. That's how I remember J-dog had the fresh things up head
We was talking about the cut the art to popped up and they started talking to acts
It's like you just you don't want to play with him the actual question
He probably thought they were backstage. He knows loud. Oh, he thought it was all after parties. He probably thought it was
VIP, you know, he thought he was gonna get a lap dance
And he saw it she said still rolling the shit was rolling
He said oh shit, let me fucking take this nigga take the shit off line so nobody can see it
You know I mean, but he got exposed
Yeah, yeah, he tried to he tried to take down the panel after right after right after he slipped up
He started walling in second. No, no, no, no, no, and then you know how safe he is
I'm enjoying the street view though, but you're driving the wrong way
I'm not walking. I'm not walking. I'm walking it.
Yo, what's your name? I'm the guy with the blue picture.
Yo.
Yeah, what's your name? What's your name buddy?
My name's Dennis the next.
Mr. X.
You got Mr. Accident Builder, Mr. Record, Mr. Gonzalez, Mrs. Subbous, and Mrs. Change.
Mr. Terror is sleeping.
Miguel, you getting dressed up for the mermaid parade, Miguel? You just going regular.
You got to get dressed up, Miguel.
No, you getting dressed up?
You got to get them a stick or try to stick?
No
You got you got to wear the shells on your titties
You got we're trying to try to have in a trident stick you have a try to stick you be all right
Yeah, you gotta
Limbo
Jay almost read over the whole lady
I'm only going I'm going six six miles an hour slow
Check it out the scenery
We put on super-dipper slow five miles
Yeah, they're trying to pass it they didn't pass it though. Yeah
Fitchie miles an hour. They're trying
But it's already ready. It's already sent loads for each vehicle. So it'll matter
Yeah, but it's stupid because like the the scooters you can go up to 30 up to 30 and
And in the in the lanes so I can go and drive the regular lanes in 30 of anything
But if you just like in a bike in a bike joints 15
See the trick about that what you entered the land you need a license plate because you can be held accountable
No, because it's not gas and you have no registration
I have no been number. I have no been you have to that's when you need to register you that's why they want you to register it
Yeah, but you have no been so how am I gonna register something with no been yes, it does each thing got a bit on it
You got a number on it somewhere
Yeah, I got a social I got a
Model number is social. Yeah
That model number is the model you want to register. Yeah, but every school is this
They're trying they tried
They took away the candidate they arrested the candidates of New York City running for mayor
That's so that's another day. Yeah. Yeah, I took the candidates to running for me
They were pushing that nigga everything in the elevator
Yeah
Here's a let me see the warrant. We see the warrant
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Don't why so bad Doug D. I gotta feel it like I think Doug D is God and that simple is that
As an alter count that he'd be writing or to look like he not you know
It's the way people speak they give yourself up you give yourself up the way you speak people can't change that pattern
You got it now about the hop on the highway
I'm happy I came in when the panel was relaxing won't relax. It was crazy drunk. I'm not getting up there now
Yeah, I was I've been listening for a little hot minute
I was too sober for that shit
So you're gonna get on why you fuck that shit fuck up your heart. No, that should keep going
I'm soaked with air, I'm listening to that shagging, it's the heuristic.
Hey, ugh.
You're the West Side next to the highway, right?
No, no, not that far, right by where the boat is on the 2nd floor, where they do the parties this year.
Oh, you need to clear it. Okay.
You're the West Side.
You're the West Side next to the highway, right?
No, no, not that far, right by where the boat is on the 2nd floor, where they do the parties this year.
Oh, you need to clear it. Okay.
You're the West Side.
You're the West Side next to the highway, right?
No, no, not that far, right by where the boat is on the 2nd floor, where they do the parties this year.
You're the West Side.
You know they be having um graduation parties on these shits and put us just outwards
Wow
Graduation party just found nine shit
And we haven't all the kids over here
Thank you look fucked up
I think a little twisted. He look like a fucking long island eyes long island with that long
Nah, they don't want to tell us man. There's no day to tell us though
We went out when I was though like what 24 years ago
Okay, it's called a freedom fighters or freedom power my back freedom powers for the freedom towers
He's not that far. Now you got the progress you got the um
And price they built in I'll show you
I
Want you to show him every shirtless New Yorker. That's what he wants. All right, like that guy that just walked past you
I want you to go follow him
If I was to go on the west side he'd be high because he'd be open because they all out there
I'm going Christopher Street. Oh my god psyche. We're not act. He tried to jump through his phone
Now nigga would jump he would jump through that phone. He'll actually trade a place. You'd be like trade a place
That's a hot guy's there
Hi guys, I don't know. I don't know about hot guys, but I say there's a lot of guys
Thank you. You've never been to New York. I
Did a couple times. Yeah
So, you know how the life is in New York, they never change. Yeah, you see this shit easy. This shit causes
floods
The shit closes all stops it from hitting the city
Yeah, it goes the closes and it goes to like right here boom
Well, what about the game on the side of it? It don't make no sense
And then and then it got it got this this shit over here. It's slides
You see that one that great right there
It slides that way
It made no sense because there's other gates on the other like you don't got a whole perimeter for that
So it's like yeah, yeah, it's stupid cuz look you got all that all open. You know what I mean
Just that one
But it got it got it got more it got more on the other side too
But did you see a difference? Did you see a difference like after rain or before they made that like when they used to rain heavy
And he should be water powers or like is it a big difference? No, it's the same same shit
But this is just a case
Yeah
Big big way somebody this is in case of another Sandy
But I don't think that should have happened not in not in my lifetime, you know
Oh
For all the water but it's stupid because it's not all the way around it's just like this part a couple as I you know
They don't do it to the whole
Downtown area
You see
There's a floodgate measurement psyche, that's what that was
Think about the scooters you get on and off you can walk it or you could ride it fastest
You see we got another one right here. Okay. They got a double one. Yeah
This shit closes tonight
It closes up to this part
It closes to right right it closes right there
And if you ever come this way there's a dude
There's a dude that he lives right here. I'm gonna show y'all
He lives on the side of the road
He inside
Tell it right in there
Wow
He live right in there. Yeah, you guys on lock. You got lights
You can tell he birds he had a fire near something or he burns a lot of smoke because you're smoking outside
Don't burn that with this fireplace. Yeah, you see it right here, right? You could that's only from a fire. Yeah, some shit
Sometimes you see them. I don't know how he washes his clothes the pump
You'll see like a close angle. He'll hang his shit. He'll put it on the fence right there. I
Know they had water gates in New York. That was the first of see I'm still learning about my city on the floor
So I don't care. I'm still learning about my 30. Thanks, Jay
But it I mean I only see it on this side like this and over there which is like what that AT Street on the other side
But uh, but before you get into that PR again, I don't see no other floodgates anywhere
So I don't even know why they just did it in this part, which is stupid
You know
So it's thick as hell
Maybe
Yeah, yeah, we have one flood. Um, Hurricane Sandy and they got they got all nervous and paranoid
The pool's about to open soon
Let's go the first swim
Let's ask the answer leavey pool
Yeah
Big pool big pool all pools is open already
And not this one not this one yet
They're supposed to be right after um Monday. All right. All right
We're supposed to be open beaches in the pools supposed to be open Monday Monday is open Monday Monday is open
Monday
Okay, right. Yeah, it's supposed to the whole weekend. Wow. Yeah
I'm gonna go to school
Kids got school so they don't want to open it while kids. You don't play hooky. You know that crazy shit
Is there dolphin around? Do you already?
I don't even think they got them in the aquarium in Brooklyn. We do have the
Yeah, yeah, they got dolphins there. They got some dolphins to on the East River sometimes
You know cash some dolphins you caught some whales once in a while, but it's not up for sure thing
But they out here
How is that out here in New York?
Somebody getting sick
Oh, well this ain't no a1 channel J. We're just gonna keep on going down
So it's gonna keep pushing a one one eight one eight, this is not a one-eighth channel
You get you get you get you know a page you welcome back
All done with the mommy duties, all done with your mommy duties, relax time before work.
Yeah, just a little bit of relax time and then I go to work at 12 and then I work until like 839 o'clock and then I'm home and then I gotta do more mom duties.
Oh shit, maybe cross the street, I didn't see that nigga.
Back at it again.
Let's sit outside. It's such a nice morning. It just is raining. It looks it looks nice in New York. It's nice over here
Yeah, he got a ticket
You know, you know, you know, I would have amped it up to um to go over there, but right right now
It's not the page today. Just just just just save yourself the drama
Well
There's a senior by here called San Cedro. It's kind of a famous like
Port City
But it's known for like, you know, there's a guy that had a bunch of exotic animals that are like illegal to have
He was ready to get a ticket, but then he freed the alligator into like yeah, the like the lake or whatever
Okay, so there's a little out. There's an alligator Reggie the alligator
It's always always seemed like we're being like a duck that there's one like it's the one dubbed it
Nice patty nobody in there
Beautiful day beautiful beautiful blue sky day
Right oh
You don't even have a registration
How you get a ticket like you know can't give him a ticket
You know you from here
Probably a brand new car. He's fucking with him
Brand new for him brand new for the guy. That's all he's from P8 and is a different story, you know
Pitching that rain that rains take our earlier, but I think the
Let me read you though
Pages so regular nature. You look at it all day long page. Let me just I really do yeah
Well, and then the bus just picked up my little child. That's where I went cuz I had a getter
anymore but
Medium-sized child
Man, they're always gonna be the baby. You can always recognize my baby
I
Yeah, thanks for the view and thanks for the view and you already hi Jack. Thank you
Okay, here we go. Oh, yeah, he's totally looks like the raid dance is working. Hey the rain stick
It is two shakes of a rain stick and there you go
That's good
Great rain we've raised that we have
Hi, Casey
Aja Arbiter Doug
Hey, yo, I don't see how that's possible, but it's always a possibility KZ
Somebody probably do got an a dolphin in the New York City apartment
You guys why does that remind me of Ace Ventura? You know what you like that's what I say
It's possible, but probably not possible
That's funny you can take your whole never will make it into the tank you never know
We should have a fire soon you guys look at we'll sit out and we'll like set up the big
Projector blow-up screen for my yard, and we'll have a little fire. Let me nice hang it on the trampoline and watch a movie in the yard
I see you had that big-ass grill to your right
We will grill us some something wonderful on here
I will absolutely do that.
Actually, I was gonna think,
I was gonna think, who says that?
I'm not even, okay.
I thought about doing like a little bit more
like random cooking stuff.
I just do whatever the fuck I'm doing in my life
when I'm on the live at home,
like if I have to cook, I'm just gonna do it.
Yeah, after I saw you cook that steak,
I was like, easy, you could cook.
Yeah.
Well, I mean if you're not if you're a Canadian or Albertan girl, especially and you can't cook a fucking steak to perfection your trash
Just saying and if you can't shop on a beer
You can't shop on a beer
Yeah
Just realized how big this deck is now that I like moved a bunch of stuff around and I think that I need to like build something or
Put a gazebo with like the nice big like
Like tool curtains on it just for like sitting and having a little tea party, you know
You got to check what movies are you to pass a boot for we go watch up here
And yeah, yeah, I'll have to definitely talk to you guys about some of that stuff because I'm not sure how to
Like if we're allowed to what just Google which movies are legal
Yeah, modern movies are legal. Yeah, and then
Vote and see you which one gets the most votes and go with that like chat pick kind of thing
Yeah, if we wanted you on this on the on the show, then you know, you can like there's movies that are made before
Certainly, I think it's like 1917 or something like that
I mean, or maybe like a little bit later, but uh, they're kind of like
Yeah, like me silent films, but yeah, but you can also you can have also people come to the stream yard and then you can
You know end the stream and then I work back stage you can play
Before that way. Yeah. Yes. Yeah, someone does that but does after it's called after our movie tonight
She does
No one night. It was really fun
That for like
Not big Tom Cruise Sam no, I just I'm not I don't know I'm really picky. I guess I don't know
Yeah, you know I notice in Tom Cruise Tom Cruise always runs
Yeah, he's a fit. He's fit. He's in all his movies. He's running here. He's running. He's running there. He's running always
He also did you notice there's kids I actually googled it because I had to know what it was because if I'm an insult somebody
I'm gonna do it like correctly, right and there's he's got this
It's called an offset like palette or something where his teeth are just a little bit offset
He's got perfect teeth, but they're just a little bit to the one side. You guys Google it right now
It's gonna you probably got that then I got that. Yeah
There's a specific name for it, but I had my morning hoot now, and I'm just kind of a little bit baked
So you're gonna have to know it for me
Yeah, I know I'm actually like, you know, like it's me chandelier like well spend Ella
We were talking about that on my life tonight. It's just like being real is everything
It's totally I totally respect and like admire and appreciate women who can like do all the cool makeup stuff, but like
I don't know just like a simple redneck chick kind of you know what I mean?
So it's just like I find if I'm like this all the time that when I do dress up
It gets the effect of the whole point of dressing up. Do you know what I mean?
Yeah
So like if basically your man sees you every day like hey babe
Beautiful hi beautiful. And then when you dress up, he's like hello gorgeous. Come in
yeah exactly instead of like you know he was being worried about waking up without makeup on
him being like what do i go to sleep with every night you know what i mean like i don't know
Just be real just be real and be comfortable with like who you are and like your natural beauty because you were made the way
That you are and your soul doesn't kind of like you could connect on that level to being comfortable in your own skin
It's like that's a saying for a reason, right?
If you're always trying to change yourself, then you're never actually your whole self. You're never your full true self, right?
But we are so attached to other people, you know, spiritually and everything, we are
and I think there's a lot of energy that can mix, so we're not even aware of that.
Well, you know, you notice if you start hanging out with somebody like a lot or you get it
Like you have a your your your spouse or whatever you start to pick up on each other's like little personality traits
You know what I mean? It's like
Humans just do that. Oh, yeah, that's inevitable
Adaptability or something like that like, you know, like you said you've been in a 90 a relationship or whatever and you you won't even catch it
But you do stuff that he used to do
We leave a little piece of ourselves with people and they leave a piece of them with selves with us
Well, you know what I mean? It's always like it's kind of just always a trade
It's like an immediate trade without like a ring or like a spoken word
You know what I mean most the time especially intimacy too. So that's where you're like
you know there's a big difference between like making love or like you know what I mean and then
fucking like there's you know what I mean like you just there's certain ways to do that right too
for your soul and your body I guess oh it's the whole thing you guys can just look it up because
I'm not gonna give you a sex ed on here that's not my job but yeah you got a comment in um in the
You know what I don't care. I like my nails. I like those nails those colors those colors the way it is the black and burgundy or black and red
They're usually like a black. I like darker nails for sure
Most of the time when you look at them in a camera you move and they're like reddish. Yeah, they're they're supposed to be like that
They're like a
It's just like a light effect. It's like a cat eye and then like an overcoat thing
So it's just an optical illusion like makeup and like most other things. Oh
That's why I was gonna say
Makeup just now on Instagram or something. I was right and there was a lady there
She looked like 80 years old or something
But she made herself look like she was 25 and I was like
Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh
Now that's the literal
Uglier catfish
Honestly, if you have to like a say you go to bed with a girl at night
And you wake up and you're like she leaves and used to be like an eyelash stuck to your cheek in a fucking hair extension
Did you ever got catfish as a female like you ever got catfish to a fake male like you go to a guy's house
And he ended up being a fat
No, cuz like I don't really like me people like that, you know, I mean like I'll usually like I don't know
I'm not like
No, how about you? Thank you. Thank you. You ever got catfish? I've never got catfish. Oh, you ever got catfish? I
Think I well, you know
People would you know people do send photos of themselves sometimes that they look a little bit different from and like sometimes they occasionally they've been like maybe
over a hundred pounds
Heavier than the photo look that you know, I just really mind but
I don't like surprises. I don't really know. I don't find it anymore
Hey kitty cats
Mr. Hux you ever been you ever been you haven't been catfished miss Dax?
I've gotten a lot of bullshit photos from ladies over the years, but never fully catfished
Like meeting somebody and then being like oh my god. That's like not that's not who you represented you
That kind of thing. Yes. I was catfished on Instagram like by like this guy. He was like in the US
Army, you know, you know for something he's really cute and like so many photos. They all have stations over in
Philippines or something. And then he's like
he was like
Let's meet when we get back and then I was like it was happy. It was like so he's like and I just on Instagram and I didn't really
Don't have like that many of your pictures up there
So then I like did I like googled
Kind of the name that was on the army uniform because it said Mason on the guy's uniform I searched
US Army Mason as I look the images and it says this photos used to catfish people
So I thought I was in Africa. I know this is English wasn't great, but
Oh
In your face
Yeah, this is not the Nigerian thing. They're called Yahoo Boys Nigeria that they
Yahoo Boys
Sounds like an energy
Yahoo Boy, yeah
Because they're going yahoo they make a fake like I can't email kind of yahoo and they use that
They'll still like send a million emails from until they get a response and this is basically
Once you get a response and you start romancing that personally
It's like it's so strange. How many people do fall for these?
Some people for hundreds of thousands of dollars. It's really it is really sad. You know, you want to
Luckily, I
figured it out in the day
Hey, babe, like you said lucky you did figure it out early you would be getting scared left to right
Yeah
Hello, oh, they're telling they're telling you they want something
You can't go inside your two little
Not all of them go outside all right all of them. This one stays inside because she's my credit card kitty
Cuz hers just well, she's not allowed outside this one. He goes outside
He's also my other credit card kitty because he had an injured leg that cost like three grand last year that I honestly
Had to take a loan out to pay for then she's too little and she's not fixed yet
And then the other guy he's my oldest cat and he just
like Rambo, like nothing is allowed to survive or live or breathe in our yard.
He kills everything. It feels so bad for it.
But he brings gifts home. Cats are good that way. They always like show their appreciation.
It's weird. I'm not going to do anything with it, but the gesture is nice
So think of pro if you if you train McCartney, you'll bring you back the goods. Yeah, yeah, absolutely
They'll always trade you things
I love animals that like work on that kind of what do you think is a barter in that trade system that like we worked on naturally
You know before we had money
We said it was straight shells and stuff. Yeah
Absolutely spices all the kinds of the things, right?
Hello
Yeah, so that guy's happy Friday guys Friday
That's because it's 20
13th Friday 13th now the 20th it's 7 20 7 or 6 20
Hey, I think we're about halfway through the year.
I was like almost over halfway through the year.
This has been the worst year of my life.
I never want to have another year like this ever again.
This year is just gonna be a write-off.
I'm gonna pretend I just had a blackout night
for the whole year and that it didn't happen.
No, I'm just kidding. It's all about lessons and
That big calligraphy wrote God. Jesus.
Pardon me?
No, somebody wrote it. Oh, that's his name. His name is extra dog.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know
Understand what they wrote there. I mean, what are you saying?
So are you okay John are you okay John?
This friend here Friday and my name my name my my handle and my my channel name is long
But holy fuck bud. That's so long and sounds like you're yelling your whole name
For someone who thinks they're in a position to criticize strangers online. You think that person would speak better English
For someone who think they are a has been elderly basement dwelling Howard Stern nobody even acknowledges anymore
Since the 90s you would have way more than 2,000 subs lol. It's like one big long
spur sentence
I said, I think I think I am
The the elderly already be on hire a business, but I don't understand
All right like that when I'm drunk. I write confusing. I write as backwards. I know you probably
You know
Elderly to
Yeah, I mean he's the you know, I think he's a maybe
70s, but he's not I mean it's not certainly not elderly. I mean so that jet black long rock star hair and
I know I never said I was Howard Spencer that he's a he's a big
Influenced on you know, it was just on my comedy and how either how would you bar show? I'm not saying I am anybody
I'm just myself
well
I've 2000 subscribers to any subscribers. I'm just
Says, I enjoy you think you are, it has been elderly howers, you would have none subs.
Okay, I mean.
Okay.
Is that English?
Those are all English words.
Yeah.
I don't understand yet, I wanted John Frank to bless our tracks
Let's dig bug. What are you doing?
He's so funny baby there
There's a little bee that we call these the babies. That's her baby. And then far bean has a baby
Oh, it's usually in her bed. Where's your baby? Get your baby. Where is it?
And that's a chunky cat. Oh, yeah
She's looking at her belly. Look at her full cut. She's a chunk of chunk. She's such a chunk. She's super saggy, too
Gravity's not her friend
Well, they're cute. She's cute. The girls play pets though. The boys are they like to hunt the girls are the bug hunters
Yeah
Give me a free reading like I could do that. I did all my chores. I just have to fold laundry, but it's not done yet
then I figure what I gotta wear to work today because it's shitty outside and
Don't know what else I have to do. Oh, yeah, I have to put fuck faces fishing backpack out on the porch
So he can grab that today too. Well, I'm gone. Anyway, that's a to-do list is almost done
You like going fishing I
Love fishing. I like to fly fish, but I love fishing in general fishing
I never went fly fishing. I never went fly fishing
It's good. It's um, it's definitely a different experience. It's very it's very unique
that's very unique um what what do you want let me peel it out
let's do
oh no i got let's use the witches deck
Let's do this just because it's on the table. I put I put so much stuff away in my back room that I'm like
I still want to go get it all so like a whole like wall of cards. I
Don't I just like to collect them. I think she who dies with the most wins
Okay, this is the literary witches Oracle
This is the deck it's very cool there's like
significant people and then there's significant, you know, animals or things
that represent something with a meaning.
We just have like these like wood floors, so they have no traction and she just oh my gosh
You have no traction. We need to get you some grippy slippy
Raven you're such a little pest
Raven just in second hey
Stop not to push us over.
Well, it's down.
It's down.
That's how we're doing everything.
We have that one spot that she don't like them at.
Got to be that one spot.
She makes eye contact with me, and then she'll do it.
She'll just inch it off every time.
And then I'll go to give her trouble, and she'll go bro,
and she'll burn away for me as fast as she can.
She's literally like a little kid.
Sometimes never when I'm not going to say that
Okay, I really can't stand off right am I?
Really coming up and then Lola's like right next to you like me angrily meow. I
Know your math. I just agree. Hey, Marie
Community. All right
Let's go. I'd like three cars. Please there's many that show me the cards. I need to see
See that? I was like putting some basketball on your computer, right?
So the book.
Um, and community I did peek on the bottom of the deck when I was shuffling,
because it kept popping now.
Just kidding, I suck.
So learning something from the communities that you're a part of, look at that, you ask me,
shall receive, I got exactly three. So learning something about the community is that you're a
part of. Are starting to play a big role in the things that you're learning in order to become
or tap into a certain part of yourself that you were always meant to be or wanted to be, but like,
Just a minute and how many times does that fucking been at requested today or brought up the lion? You know what I mean?
I got the lion from psyche earlier. Okay. Well, there you go. It's the stubble verification
And then we also have Shirley Jackson so family
Hmm
So you're building connections that are becoming you know
Close like family or you're learning from them or passing things down or they're passing knowledge down
Or this could very much be a family connection, but whatever it is. I feel like you're definitely putting a
lot more I want to say
mature
Like ascended the growth type
intellectual drive and like passion into what you're doing like it's just
coming in from a different place like you're tapping into a different side of
yourself you're learning from others and you feel like
the more you learn the more you can teach so others are learning from you as well.
I mean I could go down to the basics and be like I bet you really like to read
and I bet you really really like lines and strength like we're not does know what we're
going to do here. I feel like there's just a lot more depth to this I feel like it's just you
and I think you have a lot of pride you like to speak your truth you like to
You like to feel a sense of purpose a go-getter
I feel like my pride gets in the way a little bit sometimes it can be your downfall maybe or being too smart
I don't know. There's something about that too that comes into that break. Can you please move?
but I will read from the book from these cuz
And also like repairing something like always having the strength they're like kind of being like a generational chain breaker of some sort in your family
Um or something that was left to you with high
Responsibility that you've had to learn a lot about in order to have that success
I don't know or just you know taking pride in being a family
Oriented a person so you can take it from many different many different angles, but
Those are just what I'm getting from it
So
I will read from the book on this one though, just the Shirley Jackson thing because they're
really cool meanings.
Oh, this is my book that rips.
I hate when that happens, whenever I'll get over it.
There's just like a lot of like significant women in here and that's why it's called like
literary and has just women who've made like kind of like strange
Monumental movements and history or some sort of mark or that they left behind
Okay
So, Shirley Jackson, so domestic pleasures and domestic horrors, partnerships and children.
The fiction of Shirley Jackson, 1916 to 1965, marries the ordinary with the supernatural
and often speaks to the inhumanity's people or to the, yeah, inhumanity.
humanity's people injure. Her most famous story on the subject The Lottery was
written after rural Vermont residents painted a swastika on her house. Her
husband, a professor at Bennington College, was Jewish. Yet keen
observation and a sense of humor pervade many of her works, especially her very
She looks like that's what she did with her life, you know what I mean?
That was what she was meant to do, she looks the part that she fits where it is.
Have you heard that story page called The Lottery?
Have you heard of that story called The Lottery?
I'm reading it in college English.
No, I haven't actually.
So I was just thinking maybe I should probably look into that.
It's interesting.
It's just a story.
I don't want to give it away.
Primus do it. We're having a little dark for me. You want to take it? I don't want to
So the book, you know, it's like it's like hope, you know revelation or ignorance and the lion is
in this deck
This is such a cool deck. I love it. It's just so straightforward
So shining and mastery and strengths so kind of what I was saying before we got into like the book so it's
It's just it's having strength taking pride
You know all of the things that I mentioned before it could be a factor or just one or two
But I feel like it's a combination. I feel like you know a
Lot of the things that you've learned come from the way that you were raised, you know
It creates who we are, it conditions us, and then that's how we pass that on, you know what I mean, to our children, and it's just kind of a legacy thing.
So, you can take it for what it is. I'll leave these three cards here and I'm going to pull... mmmm.
Burry, you're so cute, you little stinky bug. I'm going to do one of these for you.
And then... we'll have some conclusion.
Go see what your sister is doing
It's really quiet in my house. It's almost eerie right now. It's weird. I like moved the furniture and now it's like echoing
Mm-hmm
Winner winner so the lights
So like I said earlier just finding like what makes you feel that abundance like that kind of cups like what makes
What you've learned like what makes you you and what do you?
Acknowledge recognize and take pride in yourself about that like what do you give yourself? Thanks for everything, you know
It's it's an uncomfortable thing to do to appreciate oneself for most people, you know
I think you should start doing that more but keep doing like all this connecting that you're doing whatever you're building
and however you're doing it whether it's on the inside for yourself or
outer or
giving and receiving like just keep doing what you're doing because it's
definitely who you're supposed to be it's it's making you
The best version of yourself that you're supposed to be especially with this knowledge
You know what I mean learning because we have to feel to heal to learn to teach like it's all just a lesson
And we're all here for each other all the time and we're supposed to be so anyways and like our ancestors
And we all have that light on the inside. We can't forget that, you know, we have we are so powerful
We create what we speak we manifest our thoughts we project and attract what we feel we have a lot more power than we think we do
You know, we're not just like a little
skin suit that just expires like we have no purpose.
So imagine yourself as being composed of energy and light
because in reality, that's precisely what you are.
You are a powerful being
and people are attracted to your brilliance.
This is a time to remember how vibrant you truly are.
So that's just fear clarifying what I said earlier
and now I'm not gonna be a broken record.
I think you get the point.
You're great. Just keep doing what you're doing and keep being the person that you are and like, you know
If you want to make changes, I think you've grown and learned enough now to be like other people can't like
Dictate what I'm gonna do or who I'm gonna be but I will take their advice for reference or for guidance
And then you take whatever you want to emulsify and not in your who you are and what you do and then you can teach
That and it's just so on and so forth, right?
Now you're pretty spot on.
Good. That's what I like to hear. I'm still, I'm safe.
You're really so, I am, I'm a skeptic and I don't really follow any of these things, but lately the more eastern traditions have
I've been a lot more accurate to where I'm at in my headspace and where I am in my life.
It's just you're vibrating at a different level, a different frequency with your ascension.
And you're more aware of having more, I guess, like...
curiosity or openness to it is definitely like a huge indicator like the biggest screen
if I could be like hey I'm ascending I'm curious about this you know what I mean and especially
if it resonates for you or it's starting to open different parts of you like I said before
in the reading plus the light card coming out um clarifies exactly what you just said
I do think that, uh, I think, uh, I think, uh, the message out, thank you, Paige, for
that.
That was just awesome.
Um, you know, from the chat, the chat is mostly wonderful, there's, you know, there's
It's weird as in the chat, but we just ignore them.
I'm surrounded by cats.
How many cats are there?
Three cats.
Hey, what's that, Chris?
Come here.
Is that what's blowing?
Hi.
Yeah, he's awesome.
Hey, so thank you, Paige, for that.
I know Den has been really appreciated that.
And you know, Miguel, how are you, Miguel?
Where's the hairs hanging out?
It's seven, they're 23 in the morning.
Didn't drink much of my second beer, so I did get a little tired, but I woke up. It's got a little sleep
Ready for the day
Back oh
Yeah, but you know it was the it was the you know emotions kind of
Ran high to the night sometimes
But you know, we know we made it out we made out to the through the night the sun comes up
always the reason should be optimistic for the future and
You know, just we just learn from our past and this we keep going. That's what the humans about
Anybody chat the chat seems quiet might be you might wrap it by 7 30 this morning because
But not for
Before half-hour, I think I've been actually probably probably more like seven hours with the
Let's see if I haven't had any clothes, but
Yeah, I've been grinding pretty pretty good here
Your page is awesome. Thank you page. Hi Katrina. How are you?
Billy slick. Thanks for being here
I'm just
Somebody's people don't see the comment. Hey Gotti. What's up? 10% of all vegan meat in the US is human meat. Well, yeah, isn't that?
Not a horrific horrific, you know, it's fair. Yeah, but there must be do it is vegan meat though
I mean, it's like is it like?
like to be on a soy
Yeah, I mean it's me so
That stuff is I mean, that's me. It's made it actually in a lab. I mean, it's I think they take soy and like grow it into
Morse I it's very bizarre how they make it. I don't know how healthy
Um, it's the long run see. Yeah. Hey, babe. So yeah, I never like to taste much of you know
I was a vegetarian for a short time, but I
Know a lot of vegetarian stuff tastes bad. Some of it's really good
They have some like something like sausage and baking you would never be able to tell it's vegetarian
anything better with some of the burgers now, but
Something about meat just does it for me
Are y'all meat eaters pay page page hunts like Elkin moose and stuff like that. She's a real hunter Fisher I
Just buy my fish tacos already
He's back
Hi my phone always dies in the middle of important shit. I'm so sorry
What do you have an iPhone?
Yes, I do have an iPhone and it hates me.
Yeah.
Anyways.
My iPad has lasted a long time, like I think my iPad is like four, four and a half years
old, but my iPhone died within a couple of years, you know, I don't think there's,
you know, I can't, hey Gotti, goodnight Christine, don't the bedbugs bite.
Yeah, I hope you got a great. Yeah, you know
So that I have the cats is
Huddling around me. Yeah, but I'm like excited because my house is like clean
I like that like a lot of times cleaning this room and it's just like so nice to be in a clean room
And I can't wait to clean the rest of everything. It's like it's like not as
That would be like just intimidating and hard to do it. It's like take forever, but it's actually really quick because it was like
I'm not bored it out. It's just a little bit messy
Okay, you know I really like about your room that like right there is it your pediment, you know your pediment
You know what pediment is?
Yeah, I kind of like I kind of thought of it more like the top triangle like the green part there
But I might be the whole thing it looks like
Yeah, so like okay, and I did that myself like okay
It wasn't green when we moved in but I like can't leave things the way that there are so I put
Ouch, I just, oh my god, I just truly hurt myself.
Okay, so I did that.
And then I did just like another little accent
over on this one to match up here.
And then I did my back, my back just accent while there too.
Because you can't go overboard with it.
It's just gonna be like a peek-a-boo color, right?
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
See like this right here is like kind of called a pediment
And it kind of reminds me we kind of reminds me of the dollar bill of the American dollar
Question before I start calling you a name is it okay if I call you a new name that I've come up with you come up for you
Are you talking to me or talking to Paige talking to you, sir
Is it a is it a sweet kind name or is it something that will be bears and the horrible me?
I'll say it's just a name. It's neither sweet nor bad
Hmm. I have a hard time. I was hard. I'm trusting that
So you see how your name is psyche awakens Terry
Yeah, tarot. Yeah, I'm gonna just start calling you Pat from now on
Yeah, Pat and people call me Pat is easier to type and stuff and I've been called Pat P. A. T. Just to capitalize P. A. T.
Like so we can with you. Oh, yes, absolutely
Yep, one day we're all gonna be like
I'll be my, I'll be my coach.
You know, there's actually a center in life character named Pat.
I don't know if there's actually a big man in a movie, I don't know if you know Pat.
But it's like, it's like by Julia Sweeney, but it's like the character is like very sexually
ambiguous.
Whereas like, you know, it looks like a man kind of, but it looks like a woman, like
a big afro.
And everyone's just confused and nobody knows.
And like, and then you always think you're going to get the answer and it's like, you
never get the answer.
Like one time Pat falls down the stairs and the guy went really want to find out past a man or woman
He's like watching Pat follow the stairs and Pat's like oh my nuts
And then the guy's oh my god, he's a guy because he has nuts and then the guy and then he runs over and then
Pat pulls like he's broken peanut shells out his pocket. He's like there goes my afternoon snack
There was peanuts in the pocket. Well, but I don't know
Real quick, I love when you have when you do this fucking English. I mean, sorry the Spanish accent you're like sea senior sea senior
Yes
Oh, yeah, I love the Spaniard people and I love the Spanish. I speak Spanish. Not that perfectly, but
Yeah, I think you know, I take it in
Junior high for about three or four years. So we're too nice. Well, yeah
And plus I lived like right by the Mexican border had us though. We've met a large Hispanic population
Why are you okay first of all?
That's that's the stupidest thing to say. I don't care if you do or do not eat animals
I do I grew up on a cattle ranch. I also native we hunt we fish
You know what I mean? The land is we're allowed to take as much as we need just don't overtake
You know what I mean? So
I and I do I do like meat. I it's part of my diet. I also eat vegetables
So I don't know do I I don't give a fuck
You don't like I do love animals just because I love them I'm not getting my fucking cats
I don't eat my horses like there's certain animals that are just off the menu. Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, cuz they don't taste as delicious. Am I right?
Well, like watch it queen. Do you think that all the meat that you eat just comes from the freezer section and fucking Walmart?
No, it comes from a farm like mine. So if I'm gonna have like I just get it here. It's abundant
It's what I have to eat just like other places on the coast have seafood and abundance and other people have you know
Other shit. It's just it's it's where you I
We just survive we're just surviving so yes
Billy Billy go to the end of kangaroo and
God he eats curry goat
Yeah, I'm not sure about the goat because I'm a camp record
So I have a kind of like an affection for the goat where I think I think they're really smart and cool
And like they do really cool things like they they can faint they can scream they can climb trees they can
Escape out of yards. They can eat anything on their own faces
Well, yeah, it's a little bit kinky. Okay, and so
Billy if Billy ate a panda bear
Yeah, well, that's interesting. See I always said I want to go to Antarctica and try like the barbecue penguin
That sounds like a delicacy I want to try I try it fresh
People eat every I mean people think if you can like
If you can, if there's like any kind of thing you can swallow and digest, people eat it.
I'm eating baby seal.
Okay.
Oh my god, you have not.
It tasted like dreams and success.
Oh, dreams.
What a weirdo dude.
It was kind of funny.
It was funny.
Did this guy come from talk your ish also?
A lot of those weirdos came from talk your ish podcast.
He's a passive aggressive type I see.
I think you all that talk ish community a bunch of weirdos
I just think you have the sense of humor of a retard
If you unicorn you gain the power of stick in sight wow, is it much like your corn a Christine's back
Sorry, I deduced the thing. Hey Arthur. I'm from hot mess summer, which went to talk your ish
Which is like eight different communities together and if you really really want to know summer
Who is the channel owner go to hot mess summer on Wednesday nights?
And watch how she helps her community. Why don't you look up her real name which she gives it to everybody?
And you'll find out a lot about her. She has spoke at the UN
Here's a patient or she has a little she's an advocate for victims
So maybe I ought to back down a little bit
I know it's me when I'm right
I mean, are there you don't know a summary or she is she doesn't have her child. Well, he's gonna stay ignorant
She uh, she's a really awesome person and I, you know, I
should have piped up
I think summer is sometime next week, right? I think summer officially starts sometime next week. Fuck you author
You're you're just not a nice person. Are you?
Are they she hasn't had a drink today either yet, isn't that right Christine?
Right, you know today I did have my green juice. No, I think somebody I think somebody pitting your Cheerios this morning
Well, it was I think it was just people up here having a cordial conversation
Arthur turns on me occasionally and like you know, he gets a little
Kermudgean this part of the whole Howard Stern, you know
But I like when you I like when I'll do a laugh and he's a laugh and I wish he
Doesn't enjoy life a lot he doesn't Arthur you really need to live life to the fullest extent. I'm very serious
Like coffee's great
Well with me have you ever heard of a coffee and coffee you got in your mouth right now
Shut your pie hole and FYI Arthur. He didn't come from the talk you're a
Community just let you know
Yeah, how did you find my shit? Like where did I meet you? I think you said you mentioned I meant
Slow state
redirected and I came up on the panel
Okay
We did uh, was it trivia and then I met Lola
Overcuse pigment sounds. Yeah, I mean
Hello, Arthur. You there? What's up? Sorry. I had a phone call. Sorry about that, brother. Okay
Yeah
Uh, we should play morning trivia. Oh my god. Yes. Yes
Real quick
Yeah, what what are Michael Jackson's pronouns
Thank you, I live to the fullest I try you know
I feel I feel energy. So like you guys can see whatever you want, but I see who y'all are
Thank you. Thank you
Okay, this is show pursuit genius edition. I don't want to play along in the chat
Thinking me and you and Vita and like a couple other people
And I'll take like things from everybody in the panel like on everybody will be a part of it all the chat
Well, I want to make because I've made a lot of different like decks like different card decks and like games and stuff like that
And like tarot decks and whatever you want to call them oracle decks as well, but I would love to make our own
Personal trivia game with like questions that we all randomly add to it
And then that would be something that we could probably get like actually, you know
Like laminated and done up really nice
And I think that it would be really really cool if we all pitched in on it
And then we just made our own fucking trivia game and then we could sell that too
Yeah
Well, I just looked at the cards and
The print is so small on these cards, I would use the bigger cards as well.
But do you guys think that would be a cool idea?
Yes.
To get your name.
What do you think?
Maybe.
I do have a question for you tarot card readers.
Sure.
Can you guys read your own future?
Um, yeah, but it's difficult in the sense of trying to like separate oneself from self in order to
It's different when okay, so I'm not just a terror reader, right?
Like I'm
channeler and path intuitive medium psychic
So it's it's different. I have a bunch of the weird little all the clairs and gifts
So it's just everybody has their own unique way of doing it, but
Um, some people have an easier time reading for themselves and others, but most readers or seers or divinators or whatever you want to call them of any type, they don't normally like to do that.
Like, all of our guides always speak to us and stuff. I'm always hearing messages, but, um, so my mom passed away in October, and like, I-
Oh, sorry to hear that.
and eats and die. You know what I mean?
Yes, that's been taxes. That's been taxes.
Exactly. So it's just a cycle of life. And yes, I miss her dearly. And yes, it was really hard. And yes, I
transmute everything into a laugh. I just just the way I deal with it. So whatever. But I can channel
anybody's loved ones like they're always around me. I see spirit all the time. I see creepy weird
shit. I see fucking loved ones.
And even like you know like your pets things like that, but I cannot fucking see my own mom or channel her
I've had to get some of my other friends
Yeah, well, I feel her in different ways because she's a part of me. Does that make sense?
So that's what I mean by like separating one's self from self. So when it comes to our self
It's like we have to take it from like an unbiased. So you don't when you're reading for other people
It's just that confidence in knowing that that message is for them, where when it's me reading my own cards or listening to my own, it's just that we need clarity too.
Just because we give clarity doesn't mean we don't need it, as well as like...
I'm always testing and like I'm a skeptic too with with being very gifted
I'm also always testing it as well
So say cards pop out or I have a thought now if it comes in more than three times
So where it comes up again or it comes out no matter what I have clarity and that has been definitely like
Signed sealed and delivered does that make sense, but there's stuff that we don't want to hear
for ourselves and so we'll put that in a different mindset like a bias. I'll just brush that off
exactly unbiased exactly that's all I'm trying to say so yes and no I prefer um you know I always
listen to my own self of course my higher self my intuition my guides but and I know stuff you
know I see things so for myself too but you don't want to believe them so sometimes it's nice to
Of course. What's the biggest rule?
That's a no-no. What's the biggest no-no rule for time card using using dark magic or for like or just like if you're gifted using your gifts
for someone's
Like for with bad intentions or for like a lower vibrational like agenda does that make sense?
So, you know, we all have light and dark in us and I love both sides of me
But I have learned in the past so say
you know say if you date somebody and they really hurt you and then you decide to be just like them
and stuff into those shoes and stoop to that level or you decide to do something malicious
there's always a kind of a penance for that so that's a golden rule not just for like people
with gifts because everybody has gifts with their intuition let's be real it's just a written rule
You know what I mean? And if you're going to do that, then there's going to be penance because it will come back to you tenfold, and that's just that's one of the written rules.
Carma.
Yeah, and that exactly falls into the line in Carma's house for sure.
And then there's nothing that we can do about that, that's just...
It's gonna come back for you in a good way or a bad way whether that's with manifesting too, right?
The universe only knows one answer and it's yes
So if we're manifesting bad thoughts, that's why is we try to keep positive just like a fucking t-shirt or a poster
You know what I mean? It's cliche, but
that's how it works so it's going to give you what you want but like you have
to really be certain you have to really like envision that you already have
those things like you just have to be very comfortable in yourself and
trusting your intuition because it's there for a reason yeah for sure
hopefully wasn't too boring for you guys I prefer that psyche at times you ask
No, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I
Yeah, yeah, well politics or like, you know, certain things are like, you know, use weird language
And sometimes we'll say no, no, no, but it's usually I don't say it just for the reason
I don't I don't I don't want to discuss politics in the show. It's like so it's like it's not like
I have people from all countries here, and I love people from all countries, and I don't want to get involved in the political side of it, so.
Yes, Billy Slick needs to answer, but yeah, but I was going to mention about the, like what, like what things are shooting you with tarot.
Yeah, Paige mentioned, like, you know, the black magic, I think part of that would be called sickle cross-watching.
Yeah, and it's it's it's a cross-watching is basically like you're like, you know
You have an X and that's you then you go to YouTube and you go to their sign
You know their sign you go there's do their sign
See a terror reader you start watching their read the readings for their sign
They try to figure out what's going on. It's kind of called cross-watching. It's like the ethics of it or murky, but
It's kind of the thing where it's like, you know, when you you read you should be tapping into like one person's energy
And so you shouldn't necessarily be
reading about other people
You know without their without the permission, you know, that's kind of like
Respectful and mindful and having discernment to you, right when you're in
It's a whole thing. So there is quite a few rules or I suppose but it's all in just like, you know
Being it's just like the ones that we are given to you. You know
Player role in society is like little civil human beings the same with the soul, right? We all just have a way of
Just treating one another and how you go about reading other people's energy because it's like being a social
Camille and you're not gonna go talk to one person like you can talk to another person. You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's a whole thing. It's a whole thing. Oh, yeah
We know we're okay, you feel like each each of these are each relationship
We have with another person is like a completely unique relationship that they have with anybody as it's like so it's like it's like a chemical
Things like chemistry in a way is that's why there's like very volatile chemicals
We put the bottles of chemicals together. They're gonna be explosions. It's a good chemicals together a kid like fusing to like gold and
You know precious metals and elements and Jeff
No, you know what your vibe your vibe attracts you try by always say that and it's like that's the most real shit too
Like so like he's trying to say like it's all a frequency and it's an energetic vibration
So everybody's going through like this crazy shit right now, and you know that I know that I know you know what I'm talking about
Okay, but it's like
Summary now, and it's just like we're kind of just shedding the skin we're making room for the old like it's the universe's way
I call it like a spiritual cattle prod. So it's moving you out of your comfort zone,
whether that be emotional or physical or whatever it is, because it's for your highest good and
for what you probably really deep down want and do think about in the night. You know what I mean?
Like sometimes shit will happen and it's either an unanswered prayer for a reason or it's an
You got to find the meaning and the purpose to all of the things in your life, whether it be a fucking song you see or a number that you see or something that you encountered in the day, you give your life purpose, everything that you do or feel in the day.
So like really, you know, and you guys all know, you know, you wouldn't be asking questions or have like a need for, you know, the someone with, you know, a reading or whatever.
you already fucking know you just need that clarification because that's all it does is it
clarifies um our intuitions you know what i mean because that connects to us that's divine giving
you a message you've been asking for or just some sort of like yay or nay a green or red flag you
Yeah, it's kind of similar I say and we can emulsify
Right, I do like it. It kind of like you know reading cards is almost like
It's a similar thing to like being a hairdresser or a bartender. It's kind of like amateur. It's like all of this
No bartender
Yeah, oh, yeah, I was the manager bartender. I've done a lot of jobs, but like you're just kind of everybody's
It's for my fucking milks the cow and then the next day she's making a fucking long island
Yeah, I make a mean fucking Caesar and they'll make a great food scene
We're going to tell her amazing, we're going to tell her amazing, I don't know about Christine or about the other one.
Well don't forget Crystal Marie, Crystal Marie's in NASA and in a pilot.
Oh I love Crystal Marie, I'm not, I said Christine sir, Christine.
Christine here, Christine's a nurse and that's like an angel.
Christine's amazing and she actually does, she's the one, oh go ahead.
I'm sorry, you know when you're walking your dog and then you get to a house and then your dog is
a smell in the lawn and then Christine comes out. Yeah, that's what she reminded me of.
The dog will probably be chasing Christine's chicken around her yard, maybe, and so trying to save the chicken, but I don't know.
If she hits her head and then she'll probably fall to sleep for all year.
Okay, okay, okay.
I mean, Arty, you're just...
Sorry, sorry, I made my time.
Thank you, thank you.
It's like, okay, you're welcome.
Thank you.
Okay.
I mean, I mean...
Thank you.
Thanks for the pancakes.
Is it like there's like a big quote. It's like it's like before you say something say is it necessary to say this
Is it is it true? It's why what if it's in the universe? I don't think about those things
I just don't know. It just seems like I know but it's just like
Like when it gets like when there's like violence violence like violence just disturbs me so
Doug saying fact. Oh, come on Doug. Doug. Yeah, okay. Is Doug the one that looks like the guy from up?
Um, I don't know. It's actually a different Doug D. Okay
Yeah
He was he was just he was just impersonating the Doug D. They can't he was trying to piggyback on him
So so I would they say oh your nice nice guy then give him a mod. He was trying to fool me
Doug I
Cannot be fooled
This week so these are not good. Do you guys just make your own at home?
Hey, thanks, right j-hydrated chips. They're so easy to make
Yeah, it's always good to make your own stuff like
We're so bad convenience, but it's not too hard to like take a few extra steps and
Make your own stuff. I love a root-baking roasted garlic. Let's take it
Garlic kind of garlic clove in half the olive oil up and foil from the oven for like four degrees for like
45 minutes pretty good put it on crackers with the cheese
Squish the whole thing into some mashed potatoes and butter
I love garlic, you know garlic. I love garlic. I love garlic. No, I just don't the only thing in this planet
I don't like like for food is water chestnuts because like I don't understand tech texturally. I understand them, but like
Otherwise, otherwise they can fuck off like I just don't care
I mean they're I know they're like some Chinese food and I don't mind it
This is kind of like to the crunchy, but you know, they're kind of taste of the other way
I wouldn't eat them raw, but in some Chinese food or decent. You're Christine back
Arthur excuse me, I'm sorry Paige
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, you're the one who sounds like that
Um, I live in a wonderful community with wonderful children even neighbors come over and swim in my pool
So yeah, not really. Um, I am one that gives to my community
I'm the one who helps my community. I'm the one my community calls when they need something
We have a lot of elderly shut in I will get their meds
I will get myself dressed no matter what I feel like in the morning no matter what I have to do
I'm waiting at that pharmacy for them. Maybe you ought to try a little kindness in your life
Could use some service that does seem like some humility and
Yeah
Some public service
It's it's calm giving back
Yes, I don't know. He's kind of nasty sometimes. I don't know. I don't know why it wasn't like really like a reason for that
We were just having that conversations and then he like kind of like
That's what he does. He tries to derail it to make himself feel better when somebody peed in his Cheerios this morning
Well, it makes you guys feel any better. I was just talking for like four minutes and I didn't have
I had it on mute.
I'm sorry, Hinch. I didn't mean to cut you off, but you know, I couldn't let that go.
No, it's been my thing today. So now I'm gonna go to work and be like, probably gonna have the same problem with the phone
and the walkie-talkie using the car. Oh my gosh.
Ah, knock on some wood.
Damn life. It's in the way
Hey, what's going on everyone
Crazy every time
I'm core bombing the channel
I think it's better not be home. He's not that he's talking about his avatar. He's always comes up
Excuse me. I was like, oh my god. God, he's
Gorb bombing your channel because that avatar is scary. I mean, I like it's a guy
Like it's like a curts you it's a good art like an art. It's artwork. Yeah
Cartoon bomb going through your head
No, it's not it's a good sort of it's just they it's just like an alien looking guy
I think he has like a needle through his
lifts or something
It's artwork for a song
Yeah, it's like
But yeah, but as was like, oh my god, he's cool bombing you. He knows what he's doing. I'm like
I can't imagine that, it's just a, it's like a phase, I don't know, but...
Alex is just out, out of my mind, nothing less.
This is, something's, uh...
But it was weird because he just...
Matured him out of the left side.
I haven't seen Alex in like over a week.
He's always been like that, Saig, for two years he's been like that.
He's just getting a little bit progressive.
like someone's like the mood the mood swings of some people that I've talked they are so
busy it's like it's like the cognitive it's like there's like
it's like an ostrich egg on top
oh where where where where we look at oh where on his body on the gaudy's
the avatar yeah it's got a lot going on
No, yeah, it's from a song called can I play it? I
Don't make it big but you can go to like my community. I'll put it in my community
Wolf got it was to put it there. Yeah, you can look it up. Just look it up. Just look it up. What's the song?
It's called can I play with madness? It's the greatest song ever written
Well, there's my measuring cup that I was looking for for 85. Oh, yeah, I'm maddened
and what and cake mix you so that's Eddie basically right yes exactly oh and it's a fist cool yes
and it deals with uh all those uh second sight and uh it it is kind of like a big egg for brains that whole album is great
but I think it's a thing A that reminds me of lamb, I don't know if you lamb this, but it's
Oh cool, the fist has piece, it has like brain, like it's holding on to brain, that's dope
Yeah, it's great
Well, great
Album, album, album is called Seventh Sun
They're eating brains?
Would you say that's Seventh Sun?
Album, they have, oh album is called Seventh Sun over Seventh Sun
Holy shit
Melissa that album right now great. Oh, you'll love it. You'll you'll be in love with them forever
Great style never
Look at their buoyant
The cutest little whisk in the whole world
I got a tiny one. I got a tiny one too. I love the little wits.
Like a little baby one. I didn't do that on camera, but yeah, like a baby one.
Just to do one egg. Yeah.
Yeah, they are so cute. When you're when you're doing like egg whites or something,
that little one is just perfect.
What do we make? Very delicious.
We're gonna make I made my kid a bagel with ham and
Like egg and everything when she went on the bus like not long ago
But I didn't eat and then I made one for her friend as well
So kind of set my breakfast with or don't for her like little boyfriend that she sits with on the bus
I gave them a pack. She's like mom
Can you get me some Skittles and I was like dude
I just bought you a huge bag of tropical Skittles that you haven't eaten yet
She goes yeah, but my boyfriend likes the berry ones, so I was like okay fine
So he got a breakfast sandwich with her this morning and a pack of berry Skittles
And now I'm going to make pancakes and I'm probably going to eat one because I have the munchies for my morning joint.
And I'm going to make a bunch and then I'm going to put them in a bag and I'm going to freeze them so that she can heat them up like so we can just heat them up on the go, right?
I do that with my granddaughter. She throws it in the microwave and toasts it and it's really nice.
30 seconds done.
It does. Breakfast is done.
A caveman picture.
A caveman, caveman, a caveman.
What's your grocery list?
Don't want me to forget to make a grocery list either.
It's safe. It'll work.
You need Alexa as I'm cooking and run out of things
or open the fridge and run out of things or the pantry.
I just say Alexa ad.
I don't need an Alexa, but I'm like,
I don't need another bitch living in my house.
I got four cats, I need my daughter, I got me.
I named mine something else.
That's why I can say Alexa without it talking
because when I go on lives or people come in my house
and they start saying Alexa, turn the lights like,
oh my gosh, tell Alexa, turn the light off.
So I renamed it.
Well, Bita actually mentioned that
because we're listening to like, she was talking to Alexa
and she's playing music or whatever and she was on live
Certain people's voices she's more sensitive to than others and so that they they can do that
And I don't know just I don't ever had that kind of thing because we live in the country and
I'm Alexa pretty much, but does it like have a voice sensitivity or
recognition? So if it's on the same tone, will it pick it up? Okay, gotcha.
And one of the reasons I do it is so funny because I have adult children that
live by me and grandchildren that live by me and even the grandkids have learned
if we take the last one how Alexa would like to put on the shopping list.
Alex is always listening. Be careful.
Yes, you did that there. You see? Come here little turd.
You get down right now.
They like to sit in the window here and then they get curious and I don't really like
obviously what the alarm's cooking but...
I was just gonna say that I lost my measuring cup but I left it exactly where I lost it last time
which was in the pancake batter mix.
What are we making again corn dogs?
We're making pancakes, but we could totally use this for a corn dog batter, they're okay
Okay, which was a lot of play music or something it's really quiet my house somebody sing to me
I
That's enough. Did Arthur get bored with us did he move on did he go get a new ball of materials?
He goes to chat to chat and does the same thing
You know what I'm looking to buy page
The neighbor boy always comes over and mows my lawn in the back and
We're talking 115 degrees outside and I just feel so bad. So have you seen one of those little off, you know, like the robo?
mowers
You know, they got the robos
Yeah
So I'm looking to buy one of those
What are they asking for something like that? Well, they're down to like three four thousand dollars
Well, what's the quality like on them? Are they like I don't know my
My my other neighbor my other neighbor has one this one always looks perfect
Well
If it can do a job for you, I mean fuck the woman doesn't need another job in a day. No one does really. No
Well, what about the neighbor boys? I really like cutting the lawn too, but like, you know, it's not my all the time job
Well, the neighbor boy kind of feel bad because I you know
Because mom says go over there and cut it go over there and cut it you swim in her pool
You you plan her yard, you know, and so he
Well, right and I just kind of
it's summer is so hot
Can I swim in your pool, Christine?
You can come over and swim in my pool, baby. No, thank you. I'm not a swimmer
Do you have floaties?
I have floaties. I'm not sure they'll work for you, but I have floaties.
I have a pineapple and I have a flamingo, but I also have paddle boards and I have a tin boat for fishing.
Will all of those things fit?
Yeah, we have a little kickboard for my grandkids. They like holding on to it.
It keeps them afloat and they kick around the pool.
Yeah.
There's one like a dinosaur. I want that one.
I find one. But you know, I can teach you to swim.
Oh, that's even better.
I teach everybody to swim in my yard.
That's good.
The liability thing, no, he's kidding.
Well, but I live in Florida.
Do you know my drownings?
There are kids under the age of 14 annually.
It's quite high.
Yeah.
Very high.
And see, I give them an incentive.
I don't let kids in the hot tub.
So if they learn to swim across the pool,
it's in the hot tub.
Okay, so that works you need to be everybody's lifeguard you got shit going on well
I stay I'm always outside when they're in the pool though always
Or yeti
Well, I didn't squish her I just like it backed up and she almost tripped me and I was probably died
But she was fine. She just scuttled away and it was like
I'll accept on my cats tail and then he slaps the crap out of me
Let's make some
I take this phone call. I'll be back behave
The product I'm still I'm still watching
Are we gonna have some cinnamon in these pancakes or no
Did put cinnamon in them. Oh good, okay, but I'm gonna like put little droplets after it
So I do like a McGrittle style for like little tiny droplets of the syrup in there and the before it flip it
When it's already like sealed on the other side, that's fancy. I'm a fancy bitch. I'm just kidding. I'm not
Oh my gosh, sometimes I wish that I didn't say anything
What about bananas we got bananas I actually don't have bananas because the girls were all over playing and they
decided to
They wanted to show me how to make some tick-tock dessert
But all they did was use all my bananas and waste my flour fuck we should have all kits it up
But like they tried and they had fun doing it. So whatever, right?
So I need to go grocery shopping I do like to do like a Costco run
But I work all the rest of the weekend, so it's probably going to be Tuesday that we do a Costco run. I think
Because they have good fruit and they have just certain things but also you have to have like
Fucking King Tutts gold to go shopping at Costco. Sometimes, you know what I mean?
With the good dollar hot dogs your perishable
Okay, this pan isn't getting hot enough and it's very annoying.
I don't have patience because I haven't noticed.
Come here, Rabie. Come say good morning.
Come on. Come on, baby here.
You big stretch. Come on. Come on.
Come on, my little yellow-eyed queen.
Good morning
What
No
Did you like schedule it ahead of time
I'm I'm saying
I guess I'm assuming you'll love it today. So I'm gonna do a stop down, you know
Yeah, check out Miguel's uh, check out Miguel's youtube channel 1130
Uh, yeah eastern time. Yes. What do you do over there, Miguel? Is it fiesta?
Not now, but you know, I got our memory be dirty for a crack, you know, Coney Island in the summer is great
Yeah, anybody's they call me on it, you know
Yeah, I bet it's but it's worse low tourist says come here summertime
Love fun they did so the fairs there and stuff
Kim, what are you telling me?
What's what I do?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Here
I guess if you take all this time to do it it comes all right
Well, you just got to put a little TLC and everything you do and take a little pride in it
And then you turn out with this little beat right here
That's like restaurant quality
well, I mean to be fair I do like also cook at the clubhouse so like
And I've cooked my entire life that's one thing I do love it's that
I'm very traditional in that sense. I do know how to cook clean and I can garden and I can on I could sustain a whole compound
I really could by myself
I'll survive when the apocalypse comes just come hang out with coca-cohonists
Hey, Jen
Pays to haunt us Pays to haunt us that should be the podcast name
Yeah
John Smith John Smith and P. John P. John you never you never a
Special
No, we gotta do we got to do it. We got to do a collaboration
from there
Go do lots of all. Oh, you don't cook. Oh, yeah
So I can pick it
Huge I do I do carpet
The most Canadian thing you don't bother you're up. Oh, it's not mrs. Both is worth, huh?
It's pearl milling
For me is danchemima it's danchemima
Boycott that boycott problem. Wow, that's crazy. Yeah
And you know what?
Did you guys ever look into the actual history of that?
Aunt Jemima went through so much just to get her name
on that and her picture on that,
and then they just took it away from her,
like ever since it worked for them.
Exactly, it's bullshit.
Yeah, I think that's ridiculous.
I'm not ever thinking of being aunt Jemima, uncle Ben,
or the...
I think a week. I was a real guy, but I'm not sure I'm like Uncle Ben. I guess was real, but I'm not sure
I think answer my was just a character creation by the by the company. I think she's really fictional, but I don't know
I don't think there was a real edge of my mom, but maybe there was real to us
He's real. She's like Santa Claus. He's like, you know, if you believe in her, she's
Look at we've got hockey stick for
I
Comes a big food review other sides crispy look it. I'll let you inspect. Oh shit. That's that's so much perfect
Oh my gosh, that's really good
Okay, and like no one's home to enjoy them with me now and so like that's kind of sad
All right, my inside America fuck you is upset. No have to go
Don't forget to listen to that album
Dude, I have literally haven't paused and queued up right now
Change your life for real. I'm not kidding you. Let me know
All right, I'll talk to you after I listen to it later
Thank you. Thanks like you by
Oh God like physically in person, and I think that they might be serial killers and it makes me remember why I don't leave my house ever
Well, I didn't finish. I thought he was but now I realize he's just a genius
Oh, I wish my kiddies could have pancakes. Sorry girls. It's with you fat little fart bean. Here's iron them up
And thanks for making pancakes with me fam. That was great
We have like six more to make because of course I might be too much better, but we'll freeze them
It's time to do a burger with it and then put that as the burger bun
Oh, you can make like a pancake burger
You're I like I like the way you think I really do. It'll be sweet and savory. You'll love it. That's my favorite
Okay, let's flip this bitch. Boom! Boom!
Professional, not professional.
And I just made a mess in my clean kitchen.
Who does that? Who cleans the kitchen all morning?
Makes everything all perfect and then it's like,
I'm just gonna make like four other meals for fun. Jesus.
Trying to prepare for my week.
End, I guess.
Weekends don't exist when you're an adult. They all blend
Yeah, let's see. Yeah, you clean as you go go. Yeah
It's something to be left, so I'll probably go to sleep hockey stick something
Aliens
Aliens, huh? I don't know if I've been, I've been, I've been seeing like all blurry all day.
Okay, it's gonna make it hard to, but the print on the tarot parts is so, or on the,
the trip was so small, I would have read it, but it was too small to read, so.
That's a tiny one. You guys haven't seen a ghost?
Have you ever seen a ghost over there?
What do you guys are?
I see ghosts all the time. They're everywhere, buddy.
Yes, I see them. What do you mean? I don't see them. Okay, so it's like a different kind of perception
It's a different kind of sight. It's here here. It's like all of the senses. So like that's what clairvoyance is, right?
Or like mediumship, so it's like
It's a different kind of sight it's so hard to explain
And everybody's works differently the way that they and spirit can show you
Themselves the way that they want to or communicate or connect in that way
That's why you know, some can flick your lights or some can use your electronics or some you they can actually manifest
Themselves, so it takes a lot of energy for them to do that. You know what I mean? So it's all about
Perception it's all about being open to it. It's all about
How they're able to or choose to show themselves or you know or can so it's just it's a whole thing
Like there's just so much to it, but yes, they're everywhere and so you've seen stuff move
You've seen the most of it. Oh, yeah, there's always stuff around me. I'm just tripping over my cat
Why do you guys think I spoke we I've spoken it all the time that was the only thing fishing and smoking weed are like
The only time my mind's ever quiet ever. There's always talking. There's always there's always so much stuff going on around me all the time
Like I'm never alone. It's insane. And I know that I'm crazy
I'm one of those people that needs visual proof of things
But my only my only story I have for spirits
Yes, I was I was coming home one day and it was like a beautiful day. It was like a like a beautiful spring day
mid-afternoon
I'm two three o'clock in the afternoon and I'm driving and I'm almost to the house
But I changed my mind. I decided to go to the mall, right?
So I decided to make a shortcut to the mall right for some reason. I don't know why don't ask me why I
Decided to cut through a cemetery
And I don't know the route
To do the shortcut through the cemetery, but I know if I go diagonally through the cemetery
I'll make it to the other side and the malls over there on that other side
Never did this before just decided to do it
So I turned into the cemetery as I'm going through the gates of the cemetery in my head at Popston
It'd be messed up if I broke down the cemetery
So I'm driving through the cemetery the trees are now, you know getting thicker so it's getting darker
But there's still it's still a beautiful day on everything, but you just can't see the sun too much. I
Swear to God. I'm not lying to you
The car just stalls there in the cemetery
While I'm driving the damn car just stalls in the middle of the damn cemetery and I can't start it up again
Call my brother he comes gives me a jump we couldn't we couldn't jump the damn car
Mm-hmm. We had to end up getting it towed the next day. We caught we asked those wrong with the car
They're like nothing. It just started up right away
Yep
This thing that's real shit
That's just it'll like shake you to your core that makes you think you know what maybe there is other things out there
You know what I mean
Don't go cut through cemeteries people
I like I would get married in a cemetery
Just you know that they actually hang out the least in cemeteries you loved ones are either with you or they're like
Doing stuff, which is so fucked up to think people are always like oh a cemetery is the most great place for a paranormal
Investigation I'm like well. Yeah, but no not at the same time
Like they're usually out with people like they're always with you and then we forget that too, right an energy can travel
They can do it for the fuck they want
but
at cemetery
Because of the residual energy even in the soil too it becomes some like a portal itself just like a mirror or
Do you ever guys ever hear you never put a cough or never put a mirror in your coffin?
No
No, well, that's the thing, but I think I'm gonna I'm gonna request that I mean I'm gonna get cremated
But like I want to be like
In between two mirrors is my urn so that I can travel I can always feed the portal
I'm gonna I'm gonna haunt the fuck out of everybody
I'll flick
I'll totally just be that ghost so like comes in toast all your bread and then puts it back in the bag
And fucks with your lights through your power bills high
I'm just kidding. I'm just thinking of adult stupid shit that drives us bananas, you know.
Okay, this is gonna be a huge pancake, you guys.
Ghosts.
But anyways, I love the paranormal. Like that's another thing I wanted to do with my channel. I quit for a long time.
Don't do paranormal hunting. Yeah, I just wanted to revamp and be like, you know, I love the paranormal
I love the spooky shit, but I'm also like, you know
I'm a bit of a softer person at the same time so like a hippie on the outside and like a golf on the inside
Does that make sense? Yes, totally. Yeah, so I don't know like nothing of the dark scares me
the only thing that scares me is spiders and like I
Don't know and like sharks probably and those are just normal people fears, but
Don't know that kind of stuff is just it's the most best, you know, like I actually go in and I do stuff like that
I do energy clearing or I don't have to be at your house like I can help you with those kinds of things
So it's a calling for sure
But I didn't know how to like I didn't want to have like a podcast
The spiritual arts channel because that's about art and
Plus the fucking others another one like that's a lot going on
So I wanted to just incorporate three of them somehow or you know what I mean
Hey, just so in tune with all that
Paranormal stuff you'd freak me out if we'd like went to like a like an old hospital or something in the middle of the night
You'd be like oh my god. Oh my god. I feel that I feel that oh my god
I'd be everybody's safety beacon. You guys will be hanging off my arm all night. What was that? What was that?
So everybody needs a creepy friend, you know
Like a creepy a good creepy not a man like fuck creep creep creep, you know, you gotta bring dynamite always bring dynamite
To a paranormal investigation they're already dead breath
Listen, I don't care. If it pops off, I'm blowing things up.
We'll have to blow up the whole house, fuck it.